(RADIO STATIC CRACKLES)
MAN: Gatekeeper,
this is Mothership.
The Four Horsemen are on the gallop.
You are a go to open the stable
door. I repeat, open the stable door.
WOMAN: The payload is secure,
and the Horsemen are en route.
(BUZZES)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
BRIDE: Make sure I look cute.
- GROOM: Whoo!
- BRIDE: Get in here.
GROOM: Vegas, baby.
BRIDE: Vegas!
GROOM: Go, baby. Yeah.
(BOTH CHEERING)
- BRIDE: We did it!
- GROOM: Yeah.
I think it went. Go, baby.
Let's go. Let's go.
("SUSPICIOUS MINDS" BY
ELVIS PRESLEY PLAYING)
(LAUGHS) Whoo!
- BRIDE: Get out of here!
- GROOM: Yeah!
♪ I can't walk out ♪
(BOTH CHEERING AND LAUGHING)
BRIDE: I love life, bitches!
Love, love, love…
What are you doing?
Get in here. I feel it!
SOLDIER 1: Any idea
what the hell we're hauling?
Why we need all this
firepower to protect it?
SOLDIER 2: Could be
anything from a briefcase nuke
to the original copy of the Constitution
but the one written in the
Founding Fathers' blood.
Right. Or like, uh…
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
…Bigfoot.
I was thinking more like
headpiece to the Staff of Ra
or, uh, Amelia Earhart but alive.
- So, the less you know, the better.
- True.
I got you a little present for
making an honest woman out of me.
(CHUCKLES) Okay. What?
Wait, what are you talking about?
Oh.
Oh, yeah.
Okay.
Get in there. All right.
You are in trouble now, mister.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
(GROOM MOANING)
("SUSPICIOUS MINDS" CONTINUES PLAYING)
♪ You can't see the tears are real ♪
♪ I'm crying ♪
♪ Yes, I'm crying ♪
SOLDIER 1: All right, I've got one.
How about the lunar lander that
was supposedly left on the moon?
SOLDIER 2: Yeah, I like the
thematic extraterrestrial reference,
seeing as we're just coming
from, uh… Well, you know.
- So you're saying there's a chance.
- Chance of what?
Chance we're hauling a…
Well, you know.
The Holy Grail.
Yeah, could be the Grail.
Not the "Grail" Grail
but the Holy Grail of things
we shouldn't be hauling.
You're gonna just
make me say it out loud?
I honestly don't…
I mean, you're being cryptic.
("SUSPICIOUS MINDS" CONTINUES PLAYING)
Oh, wow. (MOANING)
Area 51.
Secret hangar. Autopsy.
All right, I'll say it. It's an alien.
- Oh, my God!
- Look out!
SOLDIER 3: Blackwing's hurt.
Come on, guys. Hustle up.
- Let's get this thing out!
- SOLDIER 3: Hurry up!
SOLDIER 4: Get this one. Hustle, hustle.
SOLDIER 5: Multiple DOAs, sir.
Never mind. They're dead in there.
Let's get to this one. Come on.
- SOLDIER 6: Guys, get to payload two!
- SOLDIER 7: Copy that!
Mothership, this is the Four Horsemen.
Do you copy?
WOMAN: Copy. Go ahead, Horsemen.
We're in an emergency situation,
Mothership. Requesting support.
WOMAN: Copy, Horsemen.
What is the nature of your emergency?
We've been in a serious accident,
Mothership.
We got numerous fatalities for sure.
We need a medevac ASAP.
WOMAN: Copy that, Horsemen.
Dispatching medevac now.
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
Keep your comms open
while I contact the medevac.
(THUDDING)
WOMAN: Horsemen,
what is the condition of the payload?
The payload.
Uh…
Yeah, payload is compromised.
Looks like it's busted open
in the middle of the highway.
WOMAN: Stand by, Horsemen.
All right, listen carefully.
Gather whoever can walk or move and
get away from the payload immediately.
Wait, what are you telling me to do?
WOMAN: Shut the fuck up and listen to
me. Get your men out of there, Horsemen.
If they can't move, leave them.
You understand?
Get away from that
location now! Do you copy?
Yeah, yeah, I copy.
SOLDIER 8: Hey! Hey!
Leave it.
Do what?
- They said to stay away from it.
- SOLDIER 9: What?
They said stay…
(GROWLING)
(SCREECHING)
Hey, we gotta go.
You heard what they said.
We need to move now!
- (DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
- (GROWLING)
We need to go back.
They need our help!
No. There is no "they." You understand?
Everyone's fucked. Come on.
(GROANING)
Wait, wait, wait! Wait!
No, no, no. We can't stop.
We got to keep moving.
We're far enough away now.
It's okay.
It is so not okay.
All right, all right.
- (GROWLS IN THE DISTANCE)
- What was that?
(SHUSHING)
(WINGS FLUTTERING)
- (RUSTLING)
- (GROWLING DEEPLY)
It's hunting us.
(BOTH PANTING)
(RUSTLING)
- (GROWLING CONTINUES)
- (GASPS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
- (GROWLING IN THE DISTANCE)
- It's getting further away. Let's go.
- (GROANS)
- (GUN FIRING)
- Holy shit. Are you kidding me?
- That really scared me. (CHUCKLES)
(GROWLING)
(SOLDIER SCREAMING)
(GASPING)
(GROANING)
(GROWLING)
(ROARING)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
LIBERACE IMPERSONATOR: Are ya ready, boys?
A one, two, three, four…
(PLAYING PIANO)
("VIVA LAS VEGAS" BY RICHARD CHEESE
AND ALLISON CROWE PLAYING)
♪ Bright light city gonna set my soul ♪
♪ Gonna set my soul on fire ♪
♪ Got a whole lot of money
That's ready to burn ♪
♪ So get those stakes up higher ♪
♪ There's a thousand pretty women
Waitin' out there ♪
♪ And they're all living devil may care ♪
♪ And I'm just the devil
With love to spare ♪
♪ So ♪
♪ Viva Las Vegas
Viva Las Vegas ♪
♪ Viva Las Vegas ♪
♪ Ka-pow! ♪
♪ How I wish that there were
More than the 24 hours in the day ♪
♪ Even if there were 40 more
I wouldn't sleep a minute away ♪
♪ Oh, there's blackjack and poker
And the roulette wheel ♪
♪ A fortune won and lost on every deal ♪
♪ All you need's a strong heart
And a nerve of steel ♪
♪ Viva Las Vegas ♪
♪ Viva, viva
Watch out, Elvis ♪
♪ Las Vegas ♪
♪ Viva Las Vegas with your neon flashin' ♪
♪ And your one-armed bandits crashin' ♪
♪ All those hopes down the drain ♪
♪ Viva Las Vegas
Turnin' day into nighttime ♪
♪ Turnin' night into daytime ♪
♪ If you see it once
You'll never be the same again… ♪
MAN: I saw what you did there.
And now, ladies and gentlemen,
joining me at the microphone,
Ms. Allison Crowe.
ALLISON: ♪ I'm gonna keep on the run
I'm gonna have me some fun ♪
- ♪ If it costs me my very last dime ♪
- MAN: Sing it!
ALLISON: ♪ If I wind up broke up, well ♪
♪ I'll always remember
That I had a real swingin' time ♪
MAN: Ah, shoot.
ALLISON: ♪ I'm gonna give it
Everything I've got ♪
♪ Lady luck
Please let the dice stay hot ♪
♪ Let me shoot a seven with every shot ♪
♪ I'm gonna give it everything I've got ♪
♪ Whoa, viva Las Vegas ♪
♪ Viva Las Vegas ♪
BOTH: ♪ Viva Las Vegas ♪
(INAUDIBLE SHOUTING)
♪ Oh, oh, viva Las Vegas ♪
♪ Viva Las Vegas ♪
♪ Viva ♪
ALLISON: ♪ Lady luck
Please let the dice stay hot ♪
♪ Let me shoot a seven with every shot ♪
♪ I'm gonna give it everything I've got ♪
♪ A fortune won and lost ♪
♪ On every deal ♪
♪ All you need is a strong heart ♪
♪ And a nerve of steel ♪
♪ Bright light city gonna set my soul ♪
♪ Gonna set my soul on fire ♪
♪ Got a whole lot of money
That's ready to burn ♪
♪ So get those stakes up higher ♪
♪ How I wish that there were more ♪
♪ Than the 24 hours in the day ♪
♪ Even if there were 40 more ♪
♪ I wouldn't sleep a minute away ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, viva Las Vegas ♪
♪ Viva Las Vegas ♪
♪ Viva ♪
♪ Viva, viva Las Vegas ♪
REPORTER: Thousands of protesters
marched on the Capitol this morning
in response to yesterday's
historic Congressional vote
that narrowly ratified
the controversial proposal
to wipe out the last remains
of the so-called Zombie Wars,
which drew to a dramatic end
with the US military
suffering massive casualties
and being forced to retreat
as Vegas was walled off with the zombies
left inside to haunt the abandoned city.
This will mark the culmination
of the president's efforts
to fulfill his campaign promise
to exterminate
Las Vegas' undead population
by taking the extreme action of dropping
a low-yield tactical nuclear bomb
on the city of Las Vegas
in four days' time,
coinciding with sunset on
the Fourth of July holiday.
The executive order has
prompted the full evacuation
of the McCarran quarantine camp,
which has long been the
target of civil rights groups
who have argued
that no evidence of infection
has been detected in the camp.
Excuse me.
May I talk to that gentleman, please?
MAN: Hey, Scott,
you got a visitor.
Mr. Ward.
Hey. You're Bly Tanaka, right?
You want to see me?
It's not every man who
saves the secretary of defense
from a horde of flesh-eating monsters,
earns the Medal of Freedom,
only to end up…
Working at a burger joint.
Mr. Tanaka,
I am well aware of my situation.
TANAKA: Here's the thing.
There's $200 million in the
basement vault beneath the Strip.
Two hundred million the insurance
company already reimbursed me for,
un-taxable, untraceable.
Un-spendable.
TANAKA: That's where you come in.
With 96 hours left,
the government has already moved
more than half of its military presence
out of the quarantine zone,
which makes it vulnerable.
I want you to put together
a team and get it out.
In exchange,
50 million is yours to divvy up
amongst whomever you take in with you.
Intrigued?
Don't give me an answer.
Think on it for the night.
(CASH REGISTER BEEPING)
In good faith.
TANAKA: We'll talk soon, Mr. Ward.
(SNIFFS)
MAN ON TV: You should just be happy
that this is essentially
a government-funded health care solution
that will put an end to all of this.
WOMAN: Come on, Sean.
You know they're not infected.
If they were,
they would be zombies already.
They're political prisoners,
just people the government
doesn't want on the streets.
You know as well as I do, if you have
questionable immigration status,
advocate for gay rights or abortion,
the next thing you know,
they have a temperature
gun at your head
or dragging you out
of your house or your car
under the guise of public safety.
SEAN: We've tested thousands
of nukes in the Nevada desert.
This is no different.
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
MAN OVER PA: Attention detainees of
Las Vegas McCarran quarantine camp.
This facility is in an active evacuation.
Board the shuttle bus for Barstow.
Have your current
temporary health clearance card
to present to officials
as you board the shuttle.
Reminder, shuttles
will be leaving every 15 minutes.
- Hey, guys.
- Kate!
Hi. (GAGS) I can't breathe.
- You guys excited for the big move?
- Yeah!
Kate, let the kids finish packing.
Go on. Come on.
Kate, I need you to
promise me something.
In case anything happens
to me in the next few days,
just make sure the kids
make it out to Barstow. Okay?
What do you mean?
What could happen?
(SIGHS)
You know her, don't you?
The coyote.
Geeta, that is not an option.
(WHISPERING)
Kate, she helps people get in,
crack a slot machine, slip back out.
Before anyone even knows, you're gone.
That money is our ticket out of here,
or we'll be trapped in Barstow forever.
Listen, these guards,
they don't give a shit.
But for five grand,
I can buy my way out, me and my kids.
I have to get the kids out by Friday,
and I will do whatever it
takes to protect my family.
Geeta, people that go in there,
they don't always come back.
Just forget it.
- Hey, wait, wait, wait, Geeta, come on.
- Just let it go, okay?
- Well…
- GUARD: Hey.
Everything okay here, ladies?
What, you don't have
anything better to do?
Kate…
- The fuck you say to me, volunteer?
- She didn't say anything.
- Is that right, volunteer?
- GEETA: Kate.
Shut the fuck up!
Okay.
What? Were you
saying something to me?
(MOUTHING) Don't.
No, I didn't say anything.
You know, the first sign
of infection is belligerence
and actions outside of social norms.
(SIGHS)
Look at me and hold still.
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
(BEEPING)
Clear.
WOMAN: (OVER PA) Volunteers
and temporary workers,
employee shuttles
leave in five minutes.
Your turn.
If you want,
I could use my rectal thermometer.
(LAUGHS)
- (BEEPING)
- GUARD: Oh.
You're down a couple of decimal points.
You sure you're feeling all right?
- You sure you're not infected?
- I… I'm fine.
I'm fine. I'm… I feel fine.
Well,
you're both within the
margin of error, but watch it.
You better be on that bus, volunteer.
Asshole.
What were you thinking?
Do you know how easy it would
be for him to make you disappear?
All he has to say is that
you dropped a degree,
and nobody would question it, nobody.
- I know, I'm…
- You know?
I just… He…
Look, it doesn't matter.
- I'm sorry. I just…
- (SNIFFLES)
I need you to promise me that
you're not gonna do anything stupid.
Geeta, it's…
it's not worth the risk.
No, you're right.
I won't.
I promise. Okay?
Thanks.
WOMAN: …employee
shuttles leave in five minutes.
(BANGING)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(GROWLING)
(ROARING)
(SCREAMING)
Mom! (WAILING)
(GASPING AND BREATHING HEAVILY)
(RINGING)
Yes?
SCOTT: Mr. Tanaka,
I'm in a tough spot.
I don't like you very much.
So I hate giving you the
satisfaction of taking the job, but…
TANAKA: You'd best to gather your team.
You'll need a helicopter
pilot and a safecracker.
I'm gonna text you an address.
Be there at 4:00 p.m. tomorrow.
(PHONE BEEPS OFF)
He's in.
WOMAN: (IN SPANISH) I hate to ask, but…
I have to take the kids to school,
and if I can't get to my job...
Don't worry, I'll fix it.
(SIGHS IN RELIEF)
Thank you, Maria.
Don't worry about it.
Careful, I'm all greasy.
- Sharkey, give her the white loaner.
- (SHARKEY SPEAKS SPANISH)
- Gracias, Maria.
- Say hi to the kids.
WOMAN: (IN ENGLISH) Okay. Bye.
Fuck.
(SIGHS)
Hey.
(CHUCKLING) Hey!
SCOTT: So you think it's a bad idea?
MARIA: Come on, Scotty.
It's not a matter of "think."
It's a matter of "is,"
and it is a bad goddamn idea.
- SCOTT: You're out?
- I didn't say that.
SCOTT: You're in?
I didn't say that either.
But you're intrigued.
That much I'm guessing your ass
knew before you even walked in.
SCOTT: I mean, think about it.
Everything we did,
all those people we saved,
look what it got us.
But what if… what if just once,
we did something just for us?
We could die.
Yeah, we'll probably die.
- Hmm.
- (CHUCKLES)
Some of us at least.
Fifty million dollars.
Fifty million.
What's the split?
Even however many ways?
Figured you, me, and Vanderohe will
take 15 million each, assuming he'll do it.
Everybody else who isn't family…
Nobody needs to know our cut.
Now you're getting it. (CHUCKLING)
(CHUCKLES)
Who else is on your crazy-ass list?
(CHUCKLING)
(BOTTLES CLINK)
VANDEROHE: So I see
you had a visitor.
Talk to me. How'd it go?
WOMAN: Well, first time she's
come to visit me in six months.
We can't make small talk
for more than 35 minutes
without it turning into a fight.
Still, she seems happy.
That's what matters, I suppose.
I'm sure that she appreciates you,
even if you don't realize it.
- Mmm.
- I mean it.
And if she doesn't… (WHISPERS) …screw her.
(BOTH LAUGH)
VANDEROHE: That's,
uh, some heavy shit.
SCOTT: So where's your head at?
You know, when we were in it,
like, when we were really in it,
I never thought about the faces
of all the countless monsters
but now just realized, you know,
were people.
But now their faces,
that's all I see.
I don't know if being back in
would be better or worse.
God, I can't figure that out,
but I guess there is
a chance that it could be…
cathartic.
There it is.
(HELICOPTER BLADES WHIRRING)
PETERS: Would you look at that.
They should have nuked Vegas
in the early '90s, but…
- This is great.
- SCOTT: Peters!
Holy shit.
SCOTT: What's up?
- What the hell brings you here?
- (SCOTT CHUCKLES)
How's the job?
Sucks ass.
What're you guys doing here?
- Well...
- We are putting together a crew for a job.
Yeah? What does it pay?
Well, if it pans out,
you make two million
dollars for one day's work.
- Two million dollars?
- But...
PETERS: That's my share.
Just for me?
Two million dollars if it pans out?
Hundred percent. I'm in. Yeah.
You don't want to know the risks or...
Why would I want to know the risks?
Two million dollars? That's a lot of cash.
Listen, I hate my life so deeply,
if I had two million dollars,
my life would change drastically.
Yeah. Thank you. Yes.
You sure you don't want to know?
Uh…
I bet it has something
to do with a helicopter.
SCOTT: Yeah.
- I'm the helicopter guy. Yeah.
- Yeah.
- Where do I sign?
- SCOTT: Okay.
- I'm in.
- SCOTT: Thanks. Nice seeing you, bud.
She hasn't changed, has she?
Nope. Still weird as ever.
Come on. This next one's on me.
("SI SEÑOR" BY CONTROL MACHETE PLAYING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
Come on. Shit.
That's it, baby.
That's what I'm fuckin' talking about!
Mikey Guzman.
- Mikey Guzman. Name rings a bell.
- Mm-hmm.
Check this out.
This is your boy, Mikey Guzman,
taping live from East Las Vegas.
We got a group of…
I counted at least five,
but let me double-check. Hold on.
Seven. We got seven shamblers.
(GUNSHOT)
Boom, motherfucker!
Double headshot.
- (GUNSHOT)
- (WHOOPING)
- Shit!
- SCOTT: Kid's crazy.
There are Reddit forums
devoted to this guy.
Swagger, baby!
- Swagger, man. Hell, yeah.
- That's how it's done.
Thank you very much.
@GuzmanOfTheDead420.
Make sure to like and subscribe.
Yo, that motherfucker has a Rolex.
That's ten grand at least.
GUZMAN: Hey!
Qué onda, güero?
SCOTT: Mikey Guzman.
Yo, what's up?
What would you say
about making 500 grand?
I'd say,
"Who the hell do I gotta kill?"
I love him.
What are we doing here?
You told me you needed a safecracker.
Might be your missing piece.
SCOTT: How would you like to
make 250 grand for one day's work?
Oh, my God.
SCOTT: Can you crack it?
- Can I crack it?
- Yeah.
(CHUCKLES)
Can I crack it?
This is like showing me a picture of
Botticelli's Madonna of the Magnificat
and asking me if
I want to fuck her.
Okay, the man who designed
this wonderful work of art,
Hans Wagner,
he named it Der Götterdämmerung
for the final chapter
in his namesake,
Richard Wagner's epic opera,
Der Ring des Nibelungen.
- Mmm.
- SAFECRACKER: Can it be opened and by me?
I don't know.
- I honestly don't.
- Okay.
Watch your fingers, Mr. Big Hand.
But of the world's
living locksmiths,
do I represent your greatest
chance of opening it?
I can, with humility, say yes.
You're in?
It's a doorway to another realm,
my friends,
and providence has brought you to me.
We go through it together.
- By the way, what's your name?
- Scott Ward.
- SAFECRACKER: Sorry?
Dieter, Scott Ward.
("BAD MOON RISING" BY THEA GILMORE PLAYING)
♪ I see a bad moon rising ♪
♪ I see trouble on the way ♪
♪ I see earthquakes and lightnin' ♪
(GROANING)
♪ I see bad times today ♪
♪ Don't go around tonight ♪
♪ 'Cause it's bound to take your life ♪
♪ There's a bad moon on the rise ♪
♪ I hear hurricanes a-blowing ♪
Are you ready to play?
♪ I know the end is comin' soon ♪
♪ I fear rivers overflowin' ♪
♪ I hear the voice of rage and ruin ♪
♪ Don't go around tonight ♪
♪ 'Cause it's bound to take your life ♪
♪ There's a bad moon on the rise ♪
Yeah.
Scott, this is Damon.
That's Chambers.
- They're with me. They'll be on my dime.
- Okay.
- DAMON: How's it going?
- Welcome to the team.
VANDEROHE: Scott, you want
to tell me what's up with the kid?
Look at him. No offense,
but he doesn't look like
zombie killer material.
Hi, my name is Dieter, and I'm
going to open what cannot be opened.
(LAUGHS) Are you kidding me?
SCOTT: No, we need
the kid to open the safe.
We lose him, we got nothing.
(CLAPPING SLOWLY)
Let's go, guys. Bring it in.
Mr. Tanaka, team's all here.
TANAKA: Lovely to have you
all gathered here today.
Meet your target.
The Vegas Bly.
You can't fly into Vegas.
It's restricted airspace.
But you can fly out.
There is an abandoned rescue helicopter
on top of the north tower, Sodom.
If you coordinate and communicate,
this should be a simple in-and-out.
(TECHNO MUSIC PLAYING)
TANAKA: You will enter the
city with a 32-hour window.
Whatever zombies are still walking
should be no problem for a gang of
tough hombres such as yourselves.
Wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait!
(MUSIC SLOWS TO A HALT)
My apologies.
How precisely do we
do the zombie killing?
Oh, Jesus.
(LAUGHING)
SCOTT: Is there anybody else
here who hasn't killed a zombie?
(SCOFFS)
Well, we all know the basics.
Zombies, shamblers, the undead,
whatever you wanna call them,
when it comes to killing them,
it's all about the brain.
Brain.
One comes at you, shoot it in the brain.
It's that simple. Any questions?
Yes. What if I took a big rock
and smashed it into the head?
Would… would that work?
Yeah. Yeah, that, uh…
that also would still be targeting
the brain, so that would work.
Copy that.
Sorry, Mr. Tanaka,
please continue.
(TECHNO MUSIC CONTINUES PLAYING)
TANAKA: From there,
you move down the Strip.
You'll reach the casino
in less than two hours.
You go in and find the generator.
The safe, beneath the
south tower, Gomorrah…
is at the end of a hallway.
There, you'll find several
nonlethal deterrents.
You'll have to find a
way to trigger them.
Meanwhile, our fearless
pilot-slash-mechanic
fuels the helicopter.
Back at the main door,
our safecracker gets to work.
Like a surgeon or a painter,
his masterpiece rendered
in barely audible clicks.
Finally, she succumbs
to the sheer dominance
of his gentle touch.
Then, all you have to do is
load the money on the helicopter
and fly off into the sunset.
- All this…
- (SNAPS FINGERS)
…a full day before the nuke
ever leaves the launchpad.
Easy peasy Japanese-y.
(CLEARS THROAT) Sorry, sir.
We're not allowed to say that anymore.
It's "lemon squeezy" now.
Yeah, but I'm...
I think it's fine if
he's Japanese-y.
TANAKA: As you wish.
Easy peasy lemon squeezy.
Take a look.
(SIGHS IN EXASPERATION)
Oh. Okay. Good job. Good job.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Hold on.
This is the real plan? It's zombies?
Yeah, bro, what's going on?
I thought you were cool with it.
You were always talking about how, if
you saw a zombie, you'd fuck his shit up.
That was bullshit, man.
What?
DAMON: Fuck this. I'm out.
This is crazy.
You all are gonna die.
- Jesus Christ.
- DAMON: Sorry, brother.
SCOTT: Amateurs.
Hey, Damon. Wait, man.
SCOTT: All right, team,
grab your load-out bags.
See you at 6:00 a.m. sharp.
VANDEROHE: Roger that, Cap.
Now, hold up, hold up.
My name's Martin.
I'm Mr. Tanaka's head of security.
Anything you need,
you talk to me.
I can access any hardware
you might want.
I'll also be accompanying you on this job
because of my extensive
knowledge of the casino.
Any questions?
Good. See you at 0600.
DIETER: 0600?
TANAKA: How're you feeling?
SCOTT: You're insane.
You know that, right?
But if it's a choice
between dying on the Strip
and spending another day
flipping patties at the Lucky Boy,
I'll gamble on a few million.
Have you given any
thought to how you'll get in?
Yeah.
WOMAN: (OVER PA) Recent
arrivals require a full health inspection.
Barstow Quarantine Center
is a zero-tolerance facility.
Without a green health
clearance sticker on your key card,
you will not be permitted
in common areas.
SCOTT: Hey. Kate.
- What are you doing here?
- I need to talk to you.
- No. No!
- Wait. Whoa!
Just hear me out. Hear me out.
(MAN SPEAKING SPANISH OVER PA)
I have an opportunity,
and I need your help.
(LAUGHS SARCASTICALLY)
Look. I know this is
gonna sound crazy.
But do one thing for me.
For you?
Do this one thing,
and I can give you $15 million.
- Fifteen million?
- Fifteen…
You don't have $15 million.
If you do this one
thing for me, I will.
I know this is not gonna
make up for what I did…
- (SCOFFS)
- …or what type of father I was.
Yeah.
With $15 million,
you can help these people.
You can go back to school,
do whatever you want.
Whatever you do with this money,
I know will be the right thing.
(WOMAN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY OVER PA)
What one thing?
GEETA: Hey. Please! Hey. Hey.
You're the coyote, right?
Take us in. Please.
Please.
(GUN FIRING)
(SIGHS IN RELIEF)
Not bad for your first time.
- (CHUCKLES)
- Okay, I get it. I understand.
I understand what beautiful
little machine. (CHUCKLES)
Hey, don't point a gun at me.
Sorry. Sorry.
Whoo!
(VEHICLE APPROACHING)
SCOTT: Here comes our ride.
- Oh, good. You want some water?
- Yeah.
You're kidding. What is this?
What?
I swear to God, if
this whole mission
is some insane way for you to
reconnect with your daughter...
It's not, all right? Trust me.
She's a volunteer at the camp.
She's got connections.
She's just giving us a ride
into the quarantine zone.
You really think I'd
take her inside the city?
(SIGHS)
("THE END" BY THE RAVEONETTES PLAYING)
♪ This is the end ♪
♪ Beautiful friend ♪
♪ My only friend, the end… ♪
Hey, how you doing? I don't think
we've officially met. My name's Martin.
Don't talk to me. I don't trust
these people, especially you.
- Oh.
- You stay the hell away from me.
Yes, ma'am.
Ooh.
(LAUGHS)
♪ …what will it be? ♪
♪ So limitless and free ♪
♪ Desperately in need ♪
♪ Of some stranger's hand ♪
♪ In a desperate land… ♪
MAN: (OVER PA) Detainees at the
Las Vegas McCarran Quarantine Center,
this facility will be closed by
the end of the day. No personnel…
(ANNOUNCEMENT CONTINUES INDISTINCTLY)
Criminals, meet your coyote.
Does coyote girl have a name?
Lilly, but "coyote" sounds cool.
You can just call
me that if you want.
All right, I'll leave
you guys to it.
I'll meet you outside
Barstow in 24 hours.
- Okay?
- Okay.
Try not to get nuked
or murdered by the undead.
(WOMAN SPEAKING SPANISH OVER PA)
(GIRL CRYING)
KATE: Hey. Hey, hey, hey,
hey, hey. What's wrong?
Mom's gone.
(SIGHS)
- VANDEROHE: Here.
- Um…
Question.
Yes, Dieter.
You don't think I need
something bigger?
If I give you something bigger
than that, you're already dead.
Dead?
Auf Wiedersehen, dead.
Um, this belongs to where?
Give me a fucking break. Really?
Dieter, try not to piss Van off.
Thank you, sir.
Hey.
- What did you do?
- What do you mean?
(BOTH GRUNTING)
KATE: Stop!
Get off me!
- Stop!
- What the hell's going on?
The hell are you doing?
KATE: You took her in.
You took in Geeta.
- Yeah. I took her in. Her and two others.
- (GASPS)
I take a lot of people in. They
need that money to get out of here.
- You know that.
- She didn't come back.
Well, not everyone does.
- They know the risks.
- KATE: She has two kids!
- LILLY: She didn't tell me that.
- (SCOFFS)
Listen, if I knew she had kids,
I wouldn't have taken her.
Did you see her die?
No.
They went ahead. I… I hung back.
They never came out. I'm sorry.
I waited, Kate, as long as I could,
but at the end of the day...
I'm coming with you.
- No, you're not.
- Yes, I am.
We're not having this conversation.
You're not coming.
There are two kids
whose mother is lost in there.
Two kids that I help look out for.
I have to find her.
Well, tell us what she looks like.
We'll look out for her.
- You think I trust you to do that?
- Kate!
- You're not coming!
- I'm not asking you!
I'm telling you
what's gonna happen.
Come here.
Listen to me. As someone
who's seen what this looks like,
this is not a path you wanna go
down. I'm not gonna let you try.
You're gonna stay put.
We'll look for your friend.
I'll see you when we get out.
- Okay?
- No. No, not okay.
You listen.
I'm going in either way.
I can go in with you,
and you can keep me safe.
- Kate.
- Or... Or… I'll just sneak in after you,
and I'll probably die.
The choice is yours.
What's it gonna be, Dad?
(EXHALES DEEPLY)
If we see your friend, great.
But you are not to run off
looking for her. This is life or death.
And if you screw around, some
of these people are gonna die.
You understand that?
And they've got families too.
So you are never,
ever to leave my sight.
Those are my terms.
Are we clear?
Yeah. We're clear.
Guys, this is Kate,
newest member of the team.
- Hey. Hello.
- How's it going?
Scott, what the fuck?
OFFICER: You having a good
time? What's he talking about?
The bomb that's coming to kill you?
Is that what you're talking about?
That's the last bus.
Go, Speedy Gonzales! Arriba.
MAN OVER PA: This is a
mandatory evacuation zone.
- We're going to need one more guy.
- For what?
You don't know what it's
like in there. Not anymore.
- The team's big enough...
- Trust me. We need another person.
What the hell's going on here?
You want to make 20 grand?
Twenty thousand dollars?
Yeah, I'll make
20 fucking grand.
I don't fucking get it. Why
the fuck would she bring him?
Honey, easy with
the f-bombs, okay?
- KATE: Are you kidding?
- OFFICER: Chainsaw.
We're about to march into a sea of
dead people and commit grand larceny.
- But excuse me for swearing.
- That's for you.
OFFICER: Me? (CHUCKLES) Oh, yes.
(EXCLAIMS)
I got this.
Whoo!
We're gonna have some fun, yeah?
I'm telling you, you
got the right guy for this.
And also, if you happen to
get scared in there or nervous,
I want you to stay close to me.
- Mm-hmm.
- I got you.
- Thanks.
- (GUN COCKING)
What's up, bro?
Gas tank. You carry that.
Don't ever touch my saw again, okay?
Don't ever talk to her again…
bro.
- Okay. For sure.
- VANDEROHE: Good answer.
LILLY: All right,
guys, let's go!
The fuck you looking at?
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
(WIND HOWLING)
Behind me.
Put your gun up, idiot.
Hey. It's not too late to go back.
LILLY: There they
are, the shamblers,
what's left of them.
(DIETER SIGHS)
What happened to them exactly?
LILLY: What's it look like?
Weren't smart enough
to get out of the sun.
You should see what
happens when it rains.
For a few hours,
they all come back to life.
Oh, Scheisse!
Okay, let's go. Come on.
How… how much rain is…
CHAMBERS: Let's get this.
Tourists.
- (GROWLS)
- (CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS)
Hey, you're Lilly, right?
You sure know your way around here.
Well, what's it to you?
Well, maybe a lot.
How much you know about
how these things operate?
Everything there is.
- Hmm.
- LILLY: Why?
(CHUCKLES) Good to know.
DIETER: Wow, was ist das?
CHAMBERS: Holy shit. What is all this?
KATE: What happened here?
LILLY: Where the police
and military finally fell.
- Vegas' last stand.
- (GROWLING DEEPLY)
- GUZMAN: Whoa, whoa. Everybody be quiet.
- (GROWLING)
Do you hear that?
(SPEAKS FRENCH)
- What the hell is that?
- Get behind the car! Go!
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
(GROWLING CONTINUES)
What is this?
Valentine.
Valentine?
(ROARING)
MARTIN: It's a
goddamn zombie tiger.
That's crossing the line.
- CHAMBERS: Hell, yeah.
- GUZMAN: Awesome.
(CHUCKLES)
(GROWLING)
Clear.
- Los geht's.
- DIETER: Okay.
OFFICER: The hell was that?
She was one of
Siegfried and Roy's.
She guards the
beginning of their territory.
- Is there another way around?
- Not really.
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
Hey, Cummings. Let me
see your gun for a second.
What? No shot.
LILLY: Just for a second.
I like it. It's beautiful.
It's reliable too.
- Oh, yeah?
- Yeah.
Can I touch it?
- You wanna touch it?
- Yeah.
Just for a second.
CUMMINGS: Mmm.
- CUMMINGS: Oh, my…
- PETERS: Hey!
I would say I was hoping I wouldn't
have to do that, but I'd be lying.
- What are you talking about?
- What is she doing?
She just shot me. Shoot her!
They'll know we're here. They won't
care so long as we play by their rules.
- Rules? De qué habla esta pendeja?
- GUZMAN: O sea, estáloca.
If we wanna go further,
we have to make a trade.
- Trade? Really?
- CUMMINGS: No trade!
Yes. An offering to
show our subservience.
- They don't think.
- CUMMINGS: Shoot this bitch!
- If they come, we kill them.
- LILLY: You don't understand.
- They're not what you think they are.
- CUMMINGS: Shoot her in the face!
- (SCREAMING)
- We're not talking about shamblers here.
You're right. They don't think.
They just move and eat. But
we're talking about the other ones.
- The alphas.
- Yes. They're smarter. They're faster.
They're organized. Straight
out of your fucking nightmares.
CUMMINGS: Please.
You all keep talking about
the city like it's their prison.
It's not. It's their kingdom.
They won't mind us
poking around the outside
so long as we play by their rules.
- CUMMINGS: Oh my God!
- We're moving into the heart of it now.
I have a mother. I love her.
Well, everyone has a mom, you cunt,
but not everyone is an abuser
lording power over quarantined women.
(CUMMINGS SOBBING)
She's lying! That's not true.
LILLY: Shut your mouth.
I've seen what you've done to those women.
- (KICK THUDS)
- You fucking rapist.
CUMMINGS: Oh my God!
That's not true at all.
(SCREECHING IN THE DISTANCE)
- Oh, fuck, no! No!
- She's coming.
CUMMINGS: Who's coming? What's coming?
- She? What's she?
- CUMMINGS: No, please. We bonded. Please.
No. No, no, no. Don't trust her.
- DIETER: Sorry.
- CUMMINGS: No, please.
Help me. Don't go.
No, we're a team.
(GROWLING)
What the…
(SHUSHES)
(GROWLING AND SNARLING)
What… what the fuck?
(SNIFFING)
(SCREECHING)
Scheisse.
Help. Shoot this!
What the fuck is this thing?
(SNIFFING)
Listen, no. No. Hi.
- I'm not here to hurt you.
- (SCREECHING)
Come on. Help me, help
me, help me, help me.
No! No, no, no, no, no.
(SCREECHES)
CUMMINGS: Help me!
Don't do it. Just stay away.
What are you doing?
(SOBBING) No. Oh my God!
Go away. Go over there.
Go over there.
(SOBBING)
(SCREAMING) No!
Help! No!
(SCREECHING)
(CUMMINGS SCREAMING INDISTINCTLY)
(GRUNTS)
- SCOTT: You ever seen her kill anyone?
- LILLY: Couple times.
- CUMMINGS: No!
- (SCREECHING)
SCOTT: Did they come back?
LILLY: Yep, as shamblers.
CUMMINGS: No!
LILLY: My theory, this started
with one of them, an original.
CUMMINGS: Oh, my God! No!
LILLY: Whoever that
is, if he bites you...
- VANDEROHE: Then you become an alpha.
- LILLY: Exactly.
Looks like they're taking
him to the Olympus.
Good. Now we
know where not to go.
LILLY: I've never figured out
exactly how it works.
All I know is they take you in there,
and you come out like one of them,
one of the fast ones.
- So, they're taking him there to turn him.
- LILLY: Yes.
Scott, that could
be where Geeta is.
Kate, we've already
talked about this.
- KATE: We have time.
- SCOTT: It's not an option.
Fine.
That's what I thought.
So, the shithead buys us
passage, and we keep going?
Well, yeah. The shithead
should buy us some goodwill,
but I'm not about to flaunt it
by walking on their streets.
If we want to go
further, we go indoors.
Allez, let's go.
(EERIE MUSIC PLAYING)
Hey, uh, has there been
any thought given to triage?
What do you mean?
Well, I mean, obviously, the
German is the most important person
'cause he can open the safe,
but barring that,
it's got to be me, right?
Because without me, you
can't fly the chopper out of here.
So that would make me
second most important.
And I don't know if you two
are tied for third or whatever,
but I'm certainly more
important than that guy.
Sorry. I didn't know you
were listening. I am way…
(CHUCKLES) Okay, I am definitely
more important than that guy.
I don't trust that guy.
You know why he was hired?
He was hired to keep tabs on us
for when we open the safe, that
we didn't take the money and run.
We should be incentivized.
I'm not trying to be the bad guy,
but we should be incentivized
to let him die.
What? What's everybody
looking at me for?
It's a free country. People
can look at whoever they want.
Actually, it's not a free country.
We're not in America anymore.
Haven't you heard?
Which technically makes it
an even freer country, right?
Whatever.
(ALL SNARLING AND GROWLING)
What the fuck is this?
(SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY)
Stay away from me!
(SCREAMS)
(SNARLING LOUDLY)
(SCREECHING)
What the fuck?
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
What is that?
(SNARLING SOFTLY)
- (GROWLING)
- No.
(LAUGHING)
Hey.
Hey. Let me talk
to you for a second.
- I can help you. Just let me...
- (SNARLS LOUDLY)
Okay. Okay.
(BOTH SNARLING SOFTLY)
(SCREECHES)
What the fuck?
(ALL GROWLING)
No.
No. No, no!
Okay. Okay, look.
Let's just talk turkey
for a second. I...
- (SCREAMS)
- (ALL GROWLING)
- (ROARING)
- (SCREAMING)
(SCREAMING)
- (ALL SNARLING AND SCREECHING)
- (CUMMINGS SCREAMING)
DIETER: Oh, shit.
(SCREAMS)
(WHISPERS) Don't touch them.
Don't shine the
light in their eyes.
I've seen this before.
They're hibernating.
If we can't see them, how are
we supposed to move forward?
I'll mark us a path.
(CRACKS GLOW STICK)
(EERIE MUSIC PLAYING)
Go for it.
Why? You want to
check out my ass?
No. I don't trust you to have
our backs if shit goes bad.
I've been watching you,
and you're up to something.
When we all get to the casino,
I think we need to
have a little conversation
about what exactly
your role is here.
Knock yourself out.
(SNARLING SOFTLY)
Gotcha, bitch.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(GROWLING)
(GROANS)
(WHEEZING)
(GROWLING AND WHEEZING SOFTLY)
(OBJECTS CLATTERING)
(SCREAMING)
(CHAMBERS CONTINUES SCREAMING)
- (SCREAMING)
- (ALL GROWLING)
- You motherfucker.
- (TRIGGER CLICKING)
Bitch.
Fuck!
(GUN FIRING)
(CHAMBERS GRUNTING)
This way!
- Where's Chambers?
- MARTIN: She was right behind me.
- What happened? What did you do?
- I didn't do anything.
She started shooting.
I wasn't close to her.
Bullshit! She was back there
with you! I know she was!
- Buddy…
- What happened?
- You don't want to...
- Motherfucker!
She's gone! Come on.
Leave her! She's dead!
Chambers! Chambers!
Come on!
(CHAMBERS SCREAMING)
Go!
Run! Run!
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
SCOTT: Guz, come on. Let's go.
Guzman. Guz! She's gone.
We gotta move. Come on, move!
(SNARLING)
(ZOMBIE 1 SNARLS)
(ZOMBIE 2 SNARLS)
(ZOMBIE 3 SNARLS)
KATE: Lilly.
(GUN FIRES)
There's no way Geeta's alive, right?
I mean, look at these things.
Don't be so sure.
I brought a guy in once.
Lost sight of him. Had to leave
him. I thought he was dead.
Then three days later,
he came walking back out.
What happened to him?
LILLY: Said they took
him to the Olympus.
Shoved him in a room
with two other people.
The leader,
he came for them one by one.
If my guy hadn't escaped,
he would have been next.
So that's a pretty
common theme for you?
Leaving people behind.
Do you think I enjoy
having to leave people?
I'm doing what I can
to make things right.
DIETER: Sir.
Come here. Look at this.
MARIA: The hell?
Is that…
Yeah, another set of
blueprints to the safe.
(WHISPERS) Another set of blueprints.
SCOTT: Slimy bastard, Tanaka.
Tanaka had other
teams here before us.
Do you know anything about this?
That's news to me.
(SCOTT SIGHS)
Peters, get up to the roof.
Get that chopper running as fast
as possible. Cruz, go with her.
She talks too much.
Look, I'm excited to see
my friends again, okay?
Sue me.
Me and the coyote will do a
perimeter check, board up the doors.
Yeah. Kate and I are
gonna find the generators.
Backup gennie's on the third-floor roof.
That's gonna be your safer bet.
Third-floor roof. Got it.
Van, get Dieter down to the vault.
Take Guzman with you.
Roger that.
Dieter, access card for the outer doors
to the safe and the service elevators.
It's by the cashiers
windows that way.
This should get
you inside. Here.
Thank you.
(CHUCKLES) That one's mine.
I got another one.
(CHUCKLES)
All right. Everybody knows what
they're doing. Let's get it done.
Yes, sir.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
What a hunk of junk.
No la vayas a cagar, my friend.
PETERS: Right.
Bye.
What the hell is this?
Spend all his money
on that fucking miniature?
(GROWLING)
(ROARS)
MARTIN: I really hate that tiger.
It's perverse.
What was it?
Guilt finally get the better of you?
One too many out there to die?
Matter of fact, yes, it has.
That mom Kate's looking for,
did you shoot her in the leg too?
No, I just lost her.
I've never left
anyone I didn't have to
or who didn't deserve it.
You have no idea what
I've seen in those camps.
What those people
have to do to survive.
At least within these walls,
the rules are clear.
You don't see them
fucking each other over.
(SPEAKS FRENCH)
If you screw me…
two between the eyes.
Two? Why two?
The second one's just for fun.
MARTIN: Ah! Shit.
What happens now?
We wait.
SCOTT: You understand
that I had to do it, right?
Do what?
SCOTT: Put her down.
You know, all those things
they were saying… about me after.
- I want to make sure you know I loved her.
- Yeah.
We loved each other.
If I ever made it seem like
that wasn't the case, I'm sorry.
I got it. It's okay.
- You do?
- KATE: Yes.
(SIGHS)
You did what you had to do.
She was one of them. It…
It's fine. Okay?
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
Wait.
You think that's why I haven't
been talking to you all these years?
Well, it seemed like the…
- Seemed like the logical assumption. Yeah.
- (SCOFFS) No.
What you did and
what happened to her,
I never blamed
you for that, ever.
Well, I don't… I don't get it.
If it wasn't what happened,
what the hell was it?
It's not the…
It's not the fact that…
you killed my mother.
It's that you never
showed up after, okay?
You… (SIGHS)
You weren't there, Scott.
You didn't call.
You didn't visit.
You didn't… talk about it.
You didn't comfort me.
SCOTT: Yeah, you're right.
It's 'cause every
time I looked at you,
I just saw her and…
It hurt like hell.
(SIGHS)
Hurt like hell.
And then when I tried to
come back around, you just…
You seemed like you didn't want me
there, so I assumed I should stay gone.
You know, maybe there's
a chance we could still…
Still what?
I don't know.
Maybe you could look
into college somewhere.
We shouldn't need money.
I could open a restaurant.
A new food truck.
Just have a life.
I was thinking, uh…
I was thinking artisan
grilled cheese sandwiches.
Artisan grilled cheese?
Yeah, what do you think?
Mmm.
Yeah, uh…
(CLEARS THROAT) I don't
know. It's a… it's a nice idea, but…
I've spent so long hating you
that I can't just turn that off.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
- That came out meaner than I meant it to.
- (CLEARS THROAT) No, it's all right.
(CLEARS THROAT) No, I understand.
(SCOTT SIGHS)
Let's just get this done.
(CLEARS THROAT)
(ENGINE STARTS)
♪ Neons are a-gleaming
And the gamblers are a-dreaming ♪
♪ Oh, it's night life ♪
♪ Yeah, night life ♪
♪ The chips go a-spilling
And it's time to make a killing ♪
♪ Oh, it's night life… ♪
Ay, su puta madre. (KISSES)
VANDEROHE: Guz!
(ZOMBIES SCREECHING)
♪ The dice go a-turning
And you hit snake eyes ♪
♪ You can't be a quitter… ♪
- (GROWLS)
- (SCREAMING)
(SCREECHES)
(EXHALES SHARPLY)
I got the bride.
I shot her three times.
Actually, it was four.
Four.
(CHUCKLES EXCITEDLY)
Whoo-hoo!
Not zombie-killing material,
my ass, Mr. Vanderohe.
(ZOMBIE SHRIEKING)
DIETER: Whoo-hoo! Ha!
Sorry, sir. Um… All right.
Okay.
- (BEEPS)
- (GATE OPENS)
DIETER: Okay.
Götterdämmerung.
You've been here
in the dark waiting for me.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
You're so beautiful. See?
Oh, look.
There's another
team of grave robbers.
They tried to cut their way in.
(SCOFFS) That's so stupid.
You stupid poor skeletons.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, no. All they managed to do
is to screw up the card reader.
VANDEROHE: Is it another
team, or is it us, Dieter?
- Huh?
- Think about it. Us.
I mean, look at them. It's us.
It could be us in another timeline,
and we're caught
in some infinite loop
of fighting and dying,
fighting and dying, fighting and dying.
And Tanaka…
the puppet master.
Devil. God.
And we, you, me, Guz,
and the rest of the team,
simply pawns in some perverse play
where we're destined
to repeat our failures.
And finally,
in some mind-bending, ironic reveal…
it all begins again.
Cool.
Boom.
(ZOMBIES SCREECHING)
(SNARLING AND SNIFFING)
(SCREECHES)
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
Amazing.
(ZOMBIES SCREECHING)
There.
That's where the first
pressure trigger is.
It's some kind of a
booby trap, trust me.
If we could find
something to trigger it…
- There.
- I see.
By the way, I love your hair.
Thanks.
(GROWLING SOFTLY)
(GEETA WHIMPERING) Oh, God.
Oh, God.
(SNARLS)
(GEETA EXCLAIMS) No!
Oh, God.
- (GROWLS)
- (SCREAMS)
- (GROWLING)
- (ALL SCREAMING)
(GROWLS)
(GROWLING SOFTLY)
(SCREECHING)
MARTIN: Hey, sweetheart.
(GROWLING)
(SCREECHES)
(SCREAMING)
Gotcha.
(GROWLS)
(SNARLS)
(SCREAMS)
(GROWLING)
- (SNARLS)
- (GRUNTS)
(GRUNTING)
Get off me!
(GASPING)
- You okay?
- Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah.
(ZOMBIE SCREECHES)
(SCREECHING)
Good luck.
Hey, gorgeous.
Hey! Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Okay. Oh.
Easy, easy, easy. Hey, hey, hey.
Okay. Yeah.
(SNARLING)
(SCREAMING)
(GROWLS SOFTLY)
(SOBBING) No. No.
- (GROWLS)
- No! (SCREAMS)
- (SNARLING)
- (SCREAMING)
What are you doing?
You said you just needed
a vial of her blood.
MARTIN: Well, forget blood.
You know how much the whole head of
one of these things is worth to my boss,
to the government?
Mwah!
In the right hands, this is the
power to make more of them.
The power to control
your own zombie army.
That's the ultimate WMD.
LILLY: This isn't what we agreed to.
Well, you want your deal or not?
Huh?
That's what I thought.
So you keep your
goddamn mouth shut.
Okay, we need to go.
Why? They gonna come looking for
her if she doesn't radio back to base?
Her death cry.
They'll have heard it.
Once they find her body,
our trade is off.
What are they gonna do?
I don't know.
(ELEVATOR DINGS)
(GROWLING SOFTLY)
(GUZMAN CHUCKLING)
Now we're talking.
Off you go.
Come on, go get it.
That's right.
GUZMAN: Come on, fool.
(MOANING)
(GROWLING)
(SCREAMING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
I… I'm okay.
Everything's fine.
(ELEVATOR DINGS)
GUZMAN: Where
you getting all these?
(MICROWAVE DINGS)
- (GROWLS)
- (YELPS)
Who's got the hot hand?
All right, here we go.
You can taste it.
- (GRUNTS SOFTLY)
- Huh? Huh?
Okay, let's go get it.
(BLOWS)
Watch this, Guz.
You see that, Diet?
- It's not the meat, it's the heat.
- DIETER: Okay.
And the deterrent
should be releasing
right… now.
(GROANING)
DIETER: What, that's it?
(SCOFFS) Oh, wow.
That's so scary.
Oh, Scheisse!
- (CHUCKLES)
- DIETER: Fuck.
That was supposed
to be nonlethal.
- That has to be illegal, right?
- Good old Tanaka.
Guess he wasn't screwing around.
So is that it, Dieter, huh?
Is it safe now?
I think, probably.
(WHIRRING)
(GROWLS)
(SPLUTTERING) Okay.
Now, it's probably clear.
Good luck with that.
Oh, come on, Guz.
It was just getting fun.
(ENGINE WHIRRING)
Yes.
Yes! Yes!
Come on! Come on!
(EXPLODING)
(ENGINE SPUTTERS)
(METAL CLANKING)
You filthy piece of shit.
Fuck!
Oh, um…
You okay there, Dieter?
- (SPLUTTERING) I'm okay.
- VANDEROHE: Yeah?
DIETER: Um, um…
Can you help me, Mr. Vanderohe? (GAGS)
- Yeah. Absolutely.
- Thank you.
One, two, three.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
DIETER: If I can open it,
it will be either
destruction or renewal.
Death… or rebirth.
(SNAPS FINGERS)
That's heavy, brother.
But I dig it.
The decision came down to the wire,
but ultimately, the president caved
to the pressures to move the date
of the bombing off of the holiday.
This marked a reversal
of his earlier position
that dropping the nuke on
the Fourth would be, quote,
"Really cool and the
ultimate fireworks show,"
and quote, "Actually kind of
patriotic if you think about it."
Due to fears that mounting
anger from humanitarian groups
would cause the bombing
to be postponed indefinitely,
the administration has
made the dramatic choice
to not postpone the bombing
but rather to move it
up by a full 24 hours.
(SCOFFS) The fuck?
NEWSCASTER: The scheduled
drop time now coming at sunset tonight.
- Stay with us…
- MARTIN: Mother of God.
MARIA: Are you fucking kidding me?
What?
NEWSCASTER: Keep
checking back with us here.
- In related news…
- MARIA: It's insane.
…the International Society
of Elvis Impersonators…
MARTIN: Think that kid
has that safe open yet?
GUZMAN: Better get out of here.
(METAL CLANKING)
SCOTT: Peters.
PETERS: Yeah.
We got a problem.
They moved the bomb up.
Oh, nice. I'm glad they decided
to move the nuclear bomb up.
I was getting kind of antsy.
SCOTT: We've got about 90
minutes before this place is dust.
How's it going up there?
(CRACKLING)
Good. I actually found a pool.
Been working on my tan.
Gotta even this shit out.
You know what I'm talking about?
How's it going over there?
Get the safe open yet?
It's a little slower than we
thought, but… we're close.
All right. I'm just giving it
a wash and wax, so hurry up.
Just waiting on you, man.
- All set.
- (RADIO CLICKS OFF)
Son of a bitch.
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
(ELEVATOR DINGS)
- Hey, Dieter. How's that safe coming?
- (DIETER GRUNTS) Scheisse!
Scott, he's working, man.
You see this? The four locks?
You know what that is?
- SCOTT: No.
- No, of course not.
It's a rotating randomization
mechanism, right, Mr. Vanderohe?
- Affirmative.
- DIETER: Yeah.
You, Mr. Sausagefinger…
You just made me mess up, and
now we're back to ground zero.
If you mess it up
again, it locks forever.
You understand? Forever.
Okay, how long will
it take you to open it?
(SIGHS) Okay.
(WATCH BEEPING)
(BEEPING CONTINUES)
- Thirty minutes.
- Okay.
Thirty minutes of silence.
- SCOTT: You got it.
- DIETER: Silencio.
(SOFTLY) Of silence. Okay?
Mr. Vanderohe, can you
please keep your team quiet?
I need to concentrate.
Thank you.
Thirty minutes,
that's not bad. Right?
Nuclear bomb drops on us
in an hour and 20 minutes.
Right, which gives us an hour to get
to the helicopter and get out of here.
- That's plenty of time.
- Plenty.
What's the alternative?
Run for the edge of the city?
I don't think we'll make it.
No, we don't need
an alt. We trust him.
- MARIA: Yeah.
- He can do it.
MARIA: Definitely.
Right, Van?
(MUTTERING)
Yeah, no, no, no. He's got it.
- Our guy Dieter can do it.
- DIETER: Ah, fuck.
- (ZOMBIE GROWLS)
- (HORSE WHINNIES)
(CRYING)
(SCREAMS)
Must be the fire egress.
Yeah, I got it.
It's probably how the last team got in
and how those shamblers got down here.
Hey, what do you
think about tofu?
What?
Tofu. My next food truck.
I was thinking, can
make anything out of tofu.
Tofu burgers, tofu fries,
tofu milkshake, tofu cheesecake.
I don't know what that is.
Tofu cheesecake. I don't know.
I thought maybe, since everyone's
going vegan now, you know.
Humans are figuring out they're
not at the top of the food chain.
What do you think?
Yeah, it's… it's okay.
- SCOTT: Yeah.
- Keep thinking.
- SCOTT: All good up there?
- Uh, yeah. We're secure.
(GUZMAN AND MARIA SPEAKING SPANISH)
GUZMAN: Shit. (SPEAKING SPANISH)
How much we got in the cart?
I'd say 200 grand, easy.
- GUZMAN: Imagine what's in the safe.
- Check this out.
That is the most money
I've ever held in my hand.
As soon as that door opens,
it's a rounding error,
toilet paper.
I'll take it if you
don't want it.
No, that's cool. I got it.
- Are you sure?
- I got it. (CHUCKLES)
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
(DIAL CLICKING)
(MECHANISM UNLOCKS)
(SWEEPING MUSIC PLAYING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Oh, my God.
(WATCH BEEPING)
DIETER: Guys, I've… (CLEARS THROAT)
I've done it. I've done it.
Wait, what? You did it?
Like… like, "did it" did it?
(CHUCKLES)
He did it.
DIETER: The only thing
that's left is to turn the wheel.
As it was inevitable that we won.
Mr. Vanderohe, would
you do me the honor?
(TRIUMPHANT MUSIC PLAYING)
(UNLOCKS)
(INAUDIBLE SPEAKING)
All right, come on.
Let's go, guys.
We got about 20 minutes
before this place is dust.
- Let's pack this shit up and go.
- DIETER: Yeah.
SCOTT: Hey, Vanny,
where's your head at now, bud?
VANDEROHE: It's in a good place, Scott.
It's in a good fucking place.
DIETER: Mr. Vanderohe.
- VANDEROHE: Let's go, Guz. Let's get it.
- (CHUCKLES EXCITEDLY)
(GROWLING SOFTLY)
(FLESH CRUNCHING)
(ROARING)
(SCREAMING)
(ALL GROWLING)
(SCOTT GRUNTING)
Just like old times, right?
Well, not just like old times
but just as crazy.
Yeah.
What's wrong? (PANTING)
I don't know, Scott.
Hey, you can talk to me.
What's up?
- You think so?
- SCOTT: Yeah.
You're really stupid.
You know that?
SCOTT: Did I miss something?
'Cause we're richer...
I didn't come here for
the money, dumb shit.
I mean, don't get me wrong,
I'll take the millions.
But… I came here for you.
I thought we could have had
something, but then you just… went away.
It's just that seeing you again is just…
bringing it all back.
And it's not that I've been waiting.
You know, I… I haven't. (SNIFFLES)
I'm happy.
Well, I'm… I'm fine.
I just thought that… maybe…
I thought I'd fucked
that up… forever.
Forever is a long time.
I'm realizing that I've been
wrong about everything.
About you and me, me and Kate.
Have you seen Kate?
Kate?
- Hey, is Kate down there?
- GUZMAN: Not here!
- Kate!
- MARIA: Where the hell is she?
(ZOMBIES SCREECHING)
(GROWLING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(SCREECHING)
(ALL SCREECHING)
(ROARS)
SCOTT: Kate?
Kate!
Goddamn it! I know where she went.
MARIA: Scott, listen to me.
Let's think this through.
- Wait for the rest...
- There's nothing to think about.
I know where she went. She's
my daughter. I'll get her back.
- I'm coming with you.
- No, you're not.
I'm not gonna let you
go out there alone.
Thank you.
(ELEVATOR DINGS)
(ALL SNARLING)
(NECK CRACKS)
- (ALL GROWLING)
- (GRUNTING)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(PANTING)
MARTIN: This way out!
LILLY: Let's go.
- (DISTANT GROWLING)
- Let's go!
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(METAL CLANKING)
What do you think?
The money.
The money. Okay.
Guzman, cover this corner.
(DEVICE BEEPS)
(GRUNTS)
Fuck!
Come on, Dieter! Come on!
(THUDDING)
(ZOMBIES SNARLING)
MARTIN: No, no, no!
(CHUCKLES)
- LILLY: Hey, what are you doing?
- MARTIN: Whoo!
Martin, let us out of here.
(CHUCKLING) Oh, my God, I got you twice.
I got you twice.
Slow learner.
Tanaka doesn't give
a shit about the money.
What's in this bag is worth
ten times what's in that vault.
Okay, I'm gonna go kill
that dumbass pilot,
now that she's fixed the
chopper, fly myself out of here.
Au revoir.
- (CHUCKLES) Moron.
- Let us out of here!
(GROWLING)
(SNARLING)
Fuck.
(GRUNTS)
(ZOMBIES SCREECHING)
(SAW MOTOR WHIRS)
(SAW MOTOR WHIRRING)
(SNARLS)
(GRUNTING)
(SCREECHES)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
- (SCREAMING)
- (GROWLING)
(IN SLOW MOTION) No!
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
Fire in the hole!
(ZOMBIES SCREECHING)
(EXPLODING)
(GRUNTING)
Hey, baby.
You still with me?
Come on, now.
Damn it!
(GROWLING)
(GROANING)
(SCREAMING)
(GRUNTING)
(ZOMBIES SCREECHING)
LILLY: Three.
All right. We'll make a run for
that elevator. Get up to the roof.
Don't stop for anything.
(EXHALES SHARPLY)
(ENERGETIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(SCREECHES)
Go!
- (RIFLE CLICKING)
- Fuck!
Come on!
Let's go!
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(SIGHS)
("DO YOU REALLY WANT TO HURT ME"
PLAYING IN ELEVATOR)
♪ Do you really want to hurt me? ♪
(BOTH PANTING)
♪ Do you really want to make me cry? ♪
(ELEVATOR DINGS)
(SONG CONTINUES INDISTINCTLY)
(SCREECHES)
(GROWLS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(GLASS SHATTERS)
Come on! Come on!
- (ENGINE WHIRRING)
- Yeah!
Come on.
(ENGINE SPUTTERING)
Peters! What the hell?
Give me 30 seconds.
(SNARLING)
SCOTT: What the hell is that?
LILLY: The head of his queen.
Martin said he'd let everyone
out of the camps if I helped him.
If I didn't say anything.
Liar!
PETERS: Goddamn it! Come on!
Come on. Let's go. Let's go.
- I know what I'm doing. Just go!
- (SNARLS)
LILLY: I'll hold him.
Go! Now!
Go!
(GROWLS)
LILLY: That's right, motherfucker.
One more step,
and I'll blow her head off.
(ZOMBIE GROWLS)
Well, more off.
What are we doing?
Just go!
Let's go!
(GROWLING)
(GRUNTING)
(SNARLING)
(SCREECHES)
(SCREAMS)
(GROWLING)
Goddamn it.
Scott, was that a zombie
in a goddamn cape?
Just fly.
Where's the money?
There is no money.
But, Peters,
Kate's at the Olympus.
We got to go get her.
How much time do we have?
- We got about nine minutes.
- Goddamn it!
You son of a bitch!
If we do this…
you better find her, man.
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
(KATE BREATHING HEAVILY)
(PEOPLE EXCLAIMING)
Oh, my God.
- GEETA: Kate?
- Geeta.
- Kate.
- Geeta, I found you. You're alive.
- GEETA: Oh, my God, Kate. Oh, Kate.
- Oh, my God.
Kate, you came back for me.
SCOTT: Hey, Peters.
Don't screw me.
Just go!
- Are you bitten?
- No.
- He hasn't gotten to us yet.
Okay, we need to go right now.
Come with me. Come with me.
Okay.
Kate? Kate?
Kate! God.
Fuck!
- (SCREAMS)
- (CRUNCHES)
Sadie!
(SNARLS)
(GUN FIRING)
Kate!
(SNARLING)
(PANTING)
(GROWLING IN THE DISTANCE)
GEETA: Kate, let's go.
(GROWLING)
Let's go!
(INTENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
SCOTT: Kate!
(PANTING)
(GUN CLICKS)
KATE: Damn.
(SNARLS)
SCOTT: Kate!
(GRUNTING)
(SCREAMS)
She left us.
Goddamn it. She left us.
(SIGHS)
(HELICOPTER WHIRRING IN THE DISTANCE)
Wait, you guys…
you guys hear that?
I know, I know. Somewhere between
leaving your ass and saving my own,
I developed a conscience.
It's exhausting.
Get in. Come on, let's go.
(TRIUMPHANT MUSIC PLAYING)
(MENACING MUSIC PLAYING)
(GROWLING)
- SCOTT: Go, go!
- Holy shit! Hold on!
(ROARING)
(SCOTT GRUNTS)
Hold on!
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(GRUNTS)
No!
(GROANING)
(GROWLING)
(SCREAMING)
(GRUNTING, SCREAMING)
(SCREAMS)
No!
(SCREECHES)
(ALERT BEEPING RAPIDLY)
(SIGHS)
(GRUNTING)
(SCOTT GROANING)
Dad? (COUGHING)
Dad?
Hey. Hey.
Dad, I'm right…
(SOFTLY) Okay. Okay.
(BOTH BREATHING HEAVILY)
Oh, thank God you're okay.
(KATE CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
Hey. Hey, it's not so bad.
It's not so bad.
It's fine. It's not as deep…
You don't have to do that.
Don't do that.
I know what this means.
Don't.
- Hey.
- No. (SNIFFLES)
I've been thinking.
I've been thinking a lot, Kate.
(KATE SOBBING)
It's got to be lobster rolls.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY AND SNIFFLES)
You know, the food truck.
Yeah.
Scott's lobster rolls.
(BOTH CHUCKLE SOFTLY)
'Cause everybody loves
a goddamn lobster roll, right?
KATE: Yeah.
Everyone loves a
goddamn lobster roll.
Hey.
Hey, I got something for you.
(GROANING)
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
Here.
I know it's not millions, but
this should get Geeta's
kids out of the camp for good.
Here. Here, you take that.
You go and make it right.
(CRYING) Okay. Okay.
I'm so goddamn proud of you.
I love you, Kate.
(CRYING)
I'm sorry I ran.
I'm such a coward.
You're not a coward.
(SNIFFLING) You're not a coward.
You're the bravest man I know.
(CHUCKLES)
(SHAKILY) I love you so much.
I'm so sorry.
Hey.
- Yeah?
- Let me just look at you.
(CRYING)
Dad. Dad.
(GASPING)
- I'm so sorry.
- (GROWLING)
(ROARING)
(CRYING)
(SOBBING)
(SCREAMS)
(HELICOPTER APPROACHING)
("ZOMBIE ACOUSTIC" BY
THE CRANBERRIES PLAYING)
(KATE CONTINUES SOBBING)
♪ Another head hangs lowly ♪
♪ Child is slowly taken ♪
♪ And the violence… ♪
Hey!
♪ Who are we mistaken? ♪
♪ But you see, it's not me
It's not my family ♪
♪ In your head, in your head
They are fightin' ♪
♪ With their tanks and their bombs
And their bombs and their guns ♪
♪ In your head, in your head
They are cryin' ♪
♪ In your head, in your head ♪
♪ Zombie, zombie, zombie ♪
(ENGINE STARTS)
(SONG ENDS)
VANDEROHE: I would like to rent
that gray and black plane out there.
I'm sorry, sir. Unfortunately,
that's a privately owned aircraft.
I'm not able to just
rent you that plane.
- Um…
- (UNZIPS BAG)
Let me see what I can do.
FLIGHT ATTENDANT: Enjoy.
Well, that is amazing.
Honestly, how do you ladies make
that in that little kitchen back there?
It's like magic.
Voilà.
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
We should…
we should make a toast.
Oh, we can't. We're working.
No, no. Just one…
One glass, one toast. It
would make one happy man.
It'd mean a lot to me.
- What the hell? Let's do it. (CHUCKLES)
- That's the spirit.
To quote the great
Joseph Campbell, he said,
"It is by going
down into the abyss
where we recover the treasures
of life. Where you stumble,
there lies your treasure."
To the ironic twist of the unknown.
- Bottoms up.
- Cheers.
Cheers.
FLIGHT ATTENDANT: Mmm.
- That's nice.
- VANDEROHE: Hmm.
(GASPS) All right. All right.
Let's sit back down there.
There we go. Okay.
- (SIGHS)
- Here, take these.
- I'm sorry. I'm a little embarrassed.
- Okay. It's okay, honey.
I'm good. I'm good.
You don't look so good.
- Long day.
- Your skin is really cold.
So, I'm gonna let
the captain know.
No. Let me just hit the head
and splash some water on
my face. I'll be good as gold.
- Okay. All right, come on.
- VANDEROHE: Okay.
- Yep. Let's get up.
- Okay. Thank you.
(CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY)
- Let's get you in.
- VANDEROHE: It's right here?
- Yep, right there. That's it, right there.
- Yeah, okay.
- FLIGHT ATTENDANT: You sure you're okay?
- I'm fine.
- FLIGHT ATTENDANT: Okay, all right.
(SIGHS)
Come on.
(EXHALES DEEPLY)
Ooh.
(INTERCOM DINGS)
PILOT: Good evening,
this is your captain speaking.
We will be beginning our
final descent into Mexico City.
I'd like to ask you to please return to
your seat and fasten your safety belt.
- The local time is 9:30 p.m…
- (LAUGHING)
…and the temperature is 67 degrees.
(SIGHS)
Thanks for flying with us.
Fuck.
("SUSPICIOUS MINDS"
BY ELVIS PRESLEY PLAYING)
♪ We're caught in a trap ♪
♪ I can't walk out ♪
♪ Because I love you too much, baby ♪
♪ Why can't you see ♪
♪ What you're doing to me ♪
♪ When you don't believe a word I say? ♪
♪ We can't go on together ♪
- ♪ With suspicious minds ♪
♪ And we can't build our dreams ♪
♪ On suspicious minds ♪
♪ So, if an old friend I know ♪
♪ Stops by to say hello ♪
♪ Would I still see suspicion
In your eyes? ♪
♪ Here we go again ♪
♪ Asking where I've been ♪
♪ You can't see the tears are real
I'm crying ♪
♪ Yes, I'm crying ♪
♪ We can't go on together ♪
- ♪ With suspicious minds ♪
♪ And we can't build our dreams ♪
♪ On suspicious minds ♪
♪ Oh, let our love survive ♪
♪ I'll dry the tears from your eyes ♪
♪ Let's don't let a good thing die ♪
♪ When, honey
You know I've never lied to you ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah ♪
♪ We're caught in a trap ♪
♪ I can't walk out ♪
♪ Because I love you too much, baby ♪
♪ Why can't you see ♪
♪ What you're doing to me ♪
♪ When you don't believe a word I say? ♪
♪ Well, don't you know
I'm caught in a trap ♪
♪ I can't walk out ♪
♪ Because I love you too much, baby ♪
♪ Well, don't you know
I'm caught in a trap ♪
♪ I can't walk out ♪
♪ Because I love you too much, baby ♪
♪ Well, don't you know
I'm caught in a trap ♪
♪ I can't walk out ♪
♪ Because I love you too much, baby ♪
♪ Well, don't you know
I'm caught in a trap ♪
♪ I can't walk out ♪
♪ Because I love you too much, baby ♪
♪ Well, don't you know
I'm caught in a trap ♪
♪ I can't walk out ♪
♪ Because I love you too much, baby ♪
♪ Well, don't you know
I'm caught in a trap ♪
♪ I can't walk out ♪
♪ Because I love you too much, baby ♪
(SONG FADES OUT)
(SLOW PIANO MUSIC PLAYING)