There are among us a people,
gifted with a perfect memory
of all their past lives.
They call themselves... lnfl'nites.
Among the lnflm'tes,
two groups have vied for power.
On one side the believers,
dedicated to using their kno w/edge
for the protection and growth
of all humanity.
Against them stand the n/hi/ists,
who see this power as a curse.
New technologies have given the nihilists
an opportunity to end all life on earth.
And the race is on for its control.
Treadwa y, tell me you got it.
Yeah. Yeah, I got it. I got it.
Might be delayed a little.
- I'm headed to meet you now.
- Copy that.
Treadwa y, you okay?
We can't let him get the egg back.
I can't believe
bathurst would go this far.
He's not the man we remember.
Shit.
Abel, I'm gonna take a shortcut.
Meet me at the freeway.
They got it blocked off.
- Get to the base of the crane.
- Treadway, listen.
Do not go up that bridge.
Treadway? Treadway?
Abel, listen to me.
If I fail, look inside.
I don't know what miracle
you think you're gonna pull off,
but there's a 150-foot gap
in front of you.
What is his plan?
Leona. Please.
Leona, wake up. Wake up.
I'll find you in the beginning.
I love you.
Did you ever have a dream so real...
It felt like a memory?
You ever catch yourself in the mirror
and it's a surprise?
Like you expected to see
someone else's face
staring back at you.
All these people all going some where,
all doing something.
But what does it all add up to?
Maybe if I knew the answer,
all the little things
might click together.
They might make sense.
- Hey. Hi.
- E Van. Right on time.
Nice to see you. How are ya?
- Any trouble getting here?
- No. No, not at all.
Third interview this week.
- Here he is.
- Hey, gentlemen.
Hey. How are you?
- Pleasure to meet you.
- Evan, great to meet you.
Thank you for your time.
I really appreciate it.
- Right.
- Wow.
Beautiful place you have here.
Absolutely gorgeous.
I just got a couple questions
if you don't mind.
Of course.
There are a couple of question marks
in your past.
I recognize that.
You're the first face people see
when they walk into my restaurant.
And they'd be greeted with a smile.
I have had some issues in the past.
I did a full background check
on you, Mr. Mccauley.
I spoke to some of your past employers.
And you know what?
They all said the same thing.
I'm interested to hear
what they had to say.
They say you're great!
They say you're smart. He's a smart guy.
Smart guy right here, huh?
That's all good.
I guess I've got the job then.
When do I start?
Tell me about the customer you attacked.
He assaulted a waitress.
So you broke his arm.
I did. It was unintentional.
Excuse me, but he grabbed her ass.
I asked him to leave politely.
He put his hands on me.
No charges were ever filed.
Everything was dismissed.
So you just walked out
of a shift at locanda
and you never came back?
I had a personal issue.
That was six years ago.
Yeah, your manager told me
that you were institutionalized.
- For two weeks.
- Two weeks. Melanie, it's just two weeks.
Just two weeks.
Look. My struggles with mental illness
are a part of my past.
I haven't had so much
as an eye twitch since.
I think, if anything,
getting through what I've been through
only makes me stronger.
And I am 100% confident
in my ability to manage here.
Thanks for coming in today, Evan.
Please. Look, I know what it looks like.
But my illness isn't an issue
you have to worry about.
- I promise you...
- Hey, we'll be in touch, okay?
No, you won't.
Excuse me?
Look, I know the brush-off when I hear it.
Mr. Mccauley, you are clearly awesome
at dealing with conflict.
You have no idea.
Thanks for coming in. But you're right.
I don't think I will need
to be calling you.
You think you know my story
because you ran a background check
and made a couple of phone calls?
I knew yours when I shook
your well-moisturized hand.
Thank you for your time.
I get it. Ldo.
Who's going to hire
a diagnosed schizophrenic
with a history of violence,
when there's a dozen candidates out there
with spark/mg clean records?
But what's really on my mind
is if / can't get a job,
I can't pay rent this month.
I mean, dry-cleaning this suit
wasn't exactly free.
And more than that, I've gotta get
something together real quick,
because these meds, the y're running out.
And once they do, shit gets real.
Are there things you just know how to do?
Like, no one's ever showed you.
Somehow each step
in the process makes sense.
Like you're remembering it.
Not learning it.
For reals, you really
made that shit yourself, man?
- Yep.
- Damn.
Hey, yo, Ronny. Yo, Ronny.
- Evan, man.
- Hey.
As requested.
Kimotsuki-styled iron. Handcrafted.
One of a kind.
Oh, hell, yeah.
Hattori hanzo, yo.
- Damn. Nice.
- Goddamn.
Get off me.
Now, let's get this man paid.
You get high off this shit?
No. Clozapine. It's an antipsychotic.
You get paid in pills?
Evan here's on "Ronny-care."
Yeah. Dr. Ronny.
Why don't you, like,
get them at Duane reade?
'Cause Evan don't wanna talk
to shrinks every two weeks, right?
Yeah. Evan can't afford
400 bucks a month on a scrip.
Yo, Wikipedia.
- What's the capital of brakina fatso?
- Yeah.
It's pronounced Burkina Faso.
Ouagadougou.
Could I have my pills, please?
Shit, man. Forgot my count, man.
You made that up.
Damn, man!
Nah. Homeboy knows everything. He a freak.
How do you know so much?
Honestly, I wish I knew.
Makes me nuts.
Could I have my pills, please?
Dang, girl. You eyeballing my boy
like he a steak dinner.
Yo, yo. What's gunpowder made of?
74% potassium nitrate, 13% charcoal.
- Okay.
- Damn.
Impressive, man.
I said eyes on me.
Come on, Ronny.
There you go, man. Sixty packages.
That's only 55.
For real?
Close enough.
The hell it is. I live on those.
Sixty. Hey. Hey.
You wanted the real thing, right?
That is it.
That is folded over 70 times.
Carbon-treated steel.
Take your damn hands off me.
You better tell your boy
to learn how to count.
The deal was for 60 bags.
Yeah? Well, that's all we got.
You don't like it,
you can go back to bellevue.
Get the get on homeboy.
I wanna test this shit out.
Yo, what's gunpowder made of?
Hold out your arm.
Showtime.
Get up.
Put your arm there.
Now, it's your neck or arm, baby.
You choose.
Ronny, that's not a toy, bro.
Mind your business, Evan.
Come on, Ronny. This ain't funny.
Oh, god! My fingers!
I think it works, huh, Ronny?
- Cut my goddamn fingers off, man!
- You'll be all right.
Hey, sweetheart,
why don't you head on home now?
You're tripping, bro.
You are done, homey. You're a dead fool.
I don't know, Ronny.
You're talking to a guy who buys
antipsychotic medication from you.
I'm feeling a little unbalanced right now.
Maybe the best way to get
the voices in my head to stop talking
is to cut yours off.
Do you think it would help?
No. Don't fire. Don't shoot. It's cool.
We're cool, man. We're cool. All right?
Hey, dickhead. Grab my pills. Now.
There you go.
- You're crazy, man.
- If I was crazy,
I'd have chopped you up
in little pieces a long time ago.
Give me my pills.
And you listen to me, Ronny.
I'm not crazy, okay?
I'm just misunderstood. All right?
- Help!
- Leona!
NYPD picked up an Evan mccauley.
Drug deal gone south.
Cops found a sword on him.
Blade was made with a process
hasn't been used since edo Japan.
He claims he forged it himself.
Another broker-turned-h/pster blacksmith.
Oh, ye of little faith.
Are you seeing this, Nora?
- Treadwa y?
- Precisely.
If we know, bathurst knows.
Be careful.
Thanks, ll/lom.
Tell us when you're done, sir.
Can I get my phone call?
Supposed to get a phone call.
You're dressed way too nice
to be an NYPD detective, so...
Must be a doctor.
Not a thing?
No recognition at all?
I think I should feel hurt.
Do you remember... Syracuse?
Syracuse.
The siege.
Second punic war.
Where we first met.
Well, not quite the thrill ride
of the first punic war,
but sequels are tough, huh?
You disappoint me.
Well, join the club.
I notice...
You didn't sign it.
Then again...
Craftsmanship like this...
You didn't need to... did you?
I made a sword. Is that a crime?
Evan mccauley.
Diagnosed with schizophrenia at 14...
After carving the words "look inside"
into your chest with a box cutter.
Electroshock proved unhelpful.
But these...
Are not bad, eh?
- Doctor, can I...
- Please. Go ahead.
At 16, attempted suicide via car crash,
necessitating the steel plate
in your skull.
Spent the rest of your early life
bouncing around
between psych hospitals and foster homes.
Well, I only cut
a couple of his fingers off.
I don't think I'm gonna need to plead
insanity on this one, am I, doctor?
I'm curious.
"Look inside."
- Why those words?
- Why not?
Which one of these... is yours?
You can skip the...
Whatever the hell this is
because none of that is mine.
You're not supposed to have that in here.
What's going on here?
Hey, officer.
Hey, what the hell is going on here?
Pick it up.
What?
Paris.
1794.
The last meal of the comte d'anjou.
A Bordeaux.
Not a bad choice for a last meal.
Was it yours?
I wish I knew what you were talking about,
but I don't know what to tell...
Jesus!
Every time you say, "I don't know,"
this trigger gets pulled.
- Is it yours?
- I don't know...
Are you out of your mind?
- We're in a police station! Officer!
- The room is soundproof!
They won't even hear it when I put
250 grams of lead
through the back of your skull.
- Is it yours?
- Yes.
Okay, yes, it's mine. Are you happy?
Jesus!
Lying... won't help.
Look, I'm just a guy
who was at the wrong place
at the wrong time. That's all.
Last chance, Evan.
Is... it... yours?
There's the treadway I know!
Little trick I learned from you.
Hello, old friend.
Vvhoa!
Get in!
- Hold on.
- Shit!
Go! Turn! Turn!
Oh, shit!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Go! Go!
Inside!
- Hold tight.
- Oh, sh...
Cover!
What are you waiting for? Let's go!
- Go the other way!
- Take the wheel.
- What?
- Get out of the car!
Yeah, sure. Retractable steering wheel.
No problem. That's perfectly normal.
- Reverse.
- Shoot that son of a bitch.
Move! Clear the street!
Shoot the driver!
Jesus Christ!
Who are they?
Relax, it's bulletproof.
180 now!
Don't stop.
- Can I ask you a question?
- Yeah, sure.
Who the hell are you?
I'm Nora brightman.
Okay. But who was that dude back there?
Bathurst. You didn't recognize him?
No, I didn't. But clearly you did.
Well, you've known him a long time.
I've never seen that man in my life.
Him, I think I'd remember.
Well, not in this life, maybe.
Maybe I bumped into him
during the second punic war?
Or maybe it was the French revolution.
I'm bad with dates.
- You remember that?
- No.
I don't remember the French revolution.
I figured it out. I see now. I get it.
- You do?
- None of this is real.
It's a psychotic break.
I'm gonna wake up in a hospital somewhere,
drooling all over myself,
strung out on lithium.
Is that easier to believe than the idea
that maybe destiny
has something more in store for you?
Destiny? Where I come from,
we got bills to pay, rent to make.
- Nobody's got time for destiny.
- That's a shame.
I know you've been
looking for answers, Evan.
You're not crazy. You never have been.
No, I'm not crazy. I'm just delusional.
Do you ever find yourself
drawn to places you've never been?
Do you ever see a picture of a place
and just know you've been there?
Do you know things you shouldn't?
Do you pick things up fast,
almost as if you're remembering skills,
not learning them?
I've told a dozen therapists this.
I've been analyzed every way possible,
a hundred times over.
It doesn't mean anything.
Do you dream in other languages?
That's what schizophrenia is.
Different people, same head.
Well, what if it was the same person,
different lives?
- You're talking about reincarnation.
- Yeah.
You can forge a sword
because you were a blacksmith.
You speak Russian
because you were Russian.
Look, I hate to break it to you.
It's a comforting idea,
souls moving from one body to the next.
But it's basically a spiritual equivalent
of "better luck next time." Okay?
Nothing more and nothing less.
Feel safe and warm
inside all that cynicism?
- I do, actually.
- And how's that working out for you?
What, in the grand scheme of things?
Like big-picture shit? Not so great.
But I'm good. I'm surviving.
The visions you've had your entire life,
Evan, aren't hallucinations.
They're memories.
So, you're saying
that a hundred doctors were wrong?
Fifty medications didn't work
because I'm really
a reincarnated Russian blacksmith?
This is real.
I'm real.
Oh, yeah? Well, this is no version
of reincarnation I've ever heard of.
Buddhist, hindu, sikh.
They believe each life begins
with a clean slate.
The answers you've been
looking for all your life...
All you gotta do is get on that plane.
You know what I'm really
asking myself right now is?
What if the craziest thing I've heard...
And this is some crazy shit...
Is actually the first thing
that's ever made any goddamn sense?
I don't gotta go feed the cat, so...
Let's go.
Go on.
They left from a private airport.
It was an unlisted flight.
She was there fast.
Too fast.
The sword hadn't been in the system
for more than a few hours.
- Then they have a base here in New York.
- I want it found.
It will lead us to Evan mccauley.
He will lead us to the egg.
Again.
We call ourselves the infinite.
Less than 500 souls from across the globe,
all born with the ability
to remember all our past lives
and the skills we've learned
in each of them.
There are two groups within the infinites,
bathurst and the nihilists,
who just want the world to end,
and us... the believers.
And what is it that we believe?
We believe that our gift
is a responsibility.
That it's up to us to leave humanity
better off than we found it.
Yeah?
I think I'm gonna need these.
- Hey.
Thanks.
It's a long way from Arthur Avenue.
It always blows my mind.
We call it the hub.
This is the place where you're gonna get
your memories back, Evan.
We'll be landing soon.
- Recognize anything?
- I'm pretty sure I'd remember this.
It used to be dedicated
to scientific research.
Anthropology and linguistics.
All of us using what we've learned.
Life afterlife
for the advancement of mankind.
And what is it now?
Headquarters for the losing side
in the war.
Bathurst is the master of combat.
Hundreds of lifetimes.
You must be prepared for everything.
He's the apex predator in our world.
Again.
Why are they bowing?
They're hoping you're Heinrich treadway.
- Again!
- Reincarnated.
Heinrich?
It was a popular name in the '50s.
In the '505.
Great for rock 'n' roll,
but lousy for names, I guess.
The 17503.
What do I know that you need so bad?
That's why you're here, to find out.
- This is treadway's room.
- Are you asking me or telling me?
I must've really screwed up
on my last incarnation.
Why would you say that?
Have you seen where I live in this life?
That's treadway's himalaya diary.
That was me.
When I was Leona warrick.
And that was treadway.
Two days after that picture was taken,
treadway saved my life.
There's a reason you picked that book.
All this tells me is what he did.
None of it tells me who he was.
Here we can study anything and everything.
Space, time, scale. It's all relevant.
That doesn't seem like much.
Welcome to my virtual sandbox.
- Name's garrick.
- Hi.
Garrick is our head
of technology and research.
He doesn't look like much.
Goddamn, it's good to see you again.
It's nice to meet you, too.
Don't worry.
All this shit, it just gets weirder.
Okay.
Now let's get started.
Follow me.
Stand there for me, please.
Okay.
That's the guy from the police station.
Bathurst.
He and treadway were once friends.
A dozen lifetimes. Wars, peace.
They stood together
at some of the greatest moments
in human history.
Then bathurst lost faith.
For the last 300 years,
he's been looking for a way out.
He needed a way to stop reincarnating.
He wants it all to end.
That's why he made this.
The egg.
Designed to kill
every living thing on earth.
That seems a little drastic.
If there is nothing left alr've,
there's noth/ng left to reincarnate r'nto.
It attacks life at the source, DNA...
Unwinding the very fabric of existence.
Every plant, e very animal, e very person.
Mama!
Jordan!
I'm coming!
Like unplugging a computer
when a program freezes.
Only when he pulls this plug,
seven billion people will go with him.
Everything it kills
accelerates the process.
God! Holy shit, that felt freaking real!
Without you, none of us
would be here right now.
What are you talking about?
Last cycle, you raided bathurst's lab,
stole the egg, killed his Einstein
and everyone who helped build it,
leaving him with no way to recreate it.
You took the secret
of the egg's whereabouts to your grave.
Bathurst spent this entire lifetime
looking for it.
And he's getting closer and closer
to finding it every day.
That's why he tracked you down
in New York.
So I get on the plane,
you get all my memories back
and I save the whole world. That's it?
That's pretty much basically it, right?
Told you it was gonna get weird.
So, what now?
Tell me good news, Nora.
Bryan Porter.
Treadwa y had a gift with steel, didn't he?
Impeccable.
Your friends in the n ypd
were certainly impressed with it.
Unfortunately, their encryption skills
are less than impeccable.
Led us right to you.
You do know we have easier ways
of doing things now, right?
Newer...
Almost never means better.
We're going to uncover
Evan mccauley's location.
We'll brute-force your encryption.
But I'd consider it... a courtesy...
If you just...
Sped the process up.
Tell us where he is.
Okay.
I know where he is.
Of course I do.
I know exactly where he is. I just...
I, um...
I sometimes have difficulties...
With my memory.
Memory.
I remember when you used to gather honey
on the fields of marathon.
Just another reminder
of how nothing stays the same.
Would you care for some?
You know what real torture is?
Listening to you?
Real torture... isn't physical pain...
But human stupidity.
Being surrounded by it, engulfed in it.
Lifetime after lifetime.
People with their idiot grins!
Their infuriating pleasantries!
Their need for approval!
Their unctuous attempts
to be loved and validated!
They are walking, talking obituaries
on the back page of a dying newspaper,
at the bottom of a birdcage,
in the corner of a filthy living room
of a hoarder cat lady!
- And we are forced...
- You'll never understand...
- To live amongst them over and over...
- Friendship, love...
- Endlessly.
- Trust.
- That is the true definition of torture.
- You still don't understand about faith!
Faith! Blah, blah, blah!
Faith!
Faith.
I'm tired of faith.
God must show me his face.
But thank you... for enlightening me.
You kept his fucking body?
Sexy son of a bitch, isn't he?
No. He's a dead guy floating in water.
That's pretty much my worst nightmare.
Actually, it's a crotonic acid matrix.
Keeps the cells alive.
Oh. That makes it
that much better. Thank you.
We're trying to understand
the science behind what we are.
Treadway believed that humans
are capable of so much more
than we realized.
Is this what you're telling me?
I'm not living up to my potential?
I've heard that speech before.
Treadway pushed past boundaries
others might call paranormal, superhuman.
He can manipulate the energy
of the world around him.
I don't even know what that means.
What it means is you'll have skills
beyond anything you've ever imagined.
Those abilities are very deep.
Below the conscious level.
I'm down. How do we get them back?
Here, we retrain your memory.
We combine the physical and the mental
to develop new neural path ways.
Il/lemor/es are held in every organ...
Every cell in your body.
Regression takes the kind of concentration
it takes years to develop.
This is a shortcut.
We shock your mind
into syncing with the system.
It's working.
I'm seeing increased activity
in all his memory centers.
Come on.
- That's not treadway.
- Really?
He just beat you.
Treadway would've killed me.
Wow.
She wasn't kidding
about being at war, huh?
Improving the human condition.
Sometimes you do it
by painting a chapel ceiling...
Yeah. And sometimes
you drop them from a mile out.
Don't touch that.
Okay, okay.
That's no gun I've ever seen before.
We're reverse-engineering
bathurst's dethroner.
A dethroner? I mean, dude,
who's coming up with these names?
Look_.
You can't kill an infinite.
You kill the body, but...
- They get reincarnated.
- Yeah.
This implants in your head
and pulls out your consciousness,
your soul, and onto a digital chip.
Your soul gets stuck on a disk
and breaks the cycle.
Over 200 of our brothers and sisters
are lost in that digital purgatory.
You come face to face with this,
my advice... find a way
to die the old-fashioned way.
Come in.
Okay if I look around?
Be my guest.
These are all you, aren't they?
They're people I once was.
All of them.
Wow. That's cool. You look happy.
I was.
Who's that guy?
In that picture, he was Abel.
Before then, other names... other faces.
But the soul...
The soul was always him.
So, what? You loved each other
through multiple lives?
These are all the same place.
Angkor wat. What we call the beginning.
I'll find you in the beginning.
I love you.
When each of us
would find ourselves in a new life,
this is where Abel and I would go.
You're reincarnated.
How would you know where to go?
Most of us have a reawakening
that begins young.
Starts with small things, memories,
feelings about a place, dreams.
By puberty...
Most infinites have full recall.
Right around the time
they diagnosed me schizophrenic.
So what happened
if you died young and got separated?
For an infinite...
Death isn't the end, it's like...
Turning the page in a book.
Next chapter, same story.
That's crazy.
New lives, new bodies,
always meeting back at the same place.
He was dethroned.
He's trapped on a computer somewhere.
My last life, I got my memories back...
And realized he was gone.
It's not my memories that matter, Evan.
It's yours.
Your last life, in Mexico,
where did you hide the egg?
Where's the egg?
Where is it?
- He's spiking.
- Shut it down.
Hey, you're okay. You're okay.
Hey. Hey, just breathe.
- I need to get up.
- Breathe.
Kovic, check his vitals.
What happened in there, Evan?
What did you see?
Your neural network fired off
like the fourth of July.
I've been seeing this stuff all my life.
It still doesn't make any sense.
Why can't he remember anything?
Between the car accident, the electroshock
and the steel plate in his head,
his mind is fractured.
Something in there
won't let the memories flow.
I can't get them out.
I'm afraid the artisan is our last hope.
He'll achieve recall soon.
If he hasn't already.
Hundreds of lifetimes,
and it all comes down to these few hours.
If we don't find him...
Before he gets his memories back,
we lose the egg...
Forever.
The wheels keep turning and we can never...
Escape.
We go at dawn.
It's been a while, Otto.
No one's called me by that name in...
So many lifetimes.
Hello, my love.
What happened to you?
You were so beautiful.
As were you.
You don't miss it...
The agility...
The vibrancy...
Being confined to this?
You see me as something broken. I don't.
You're the cripple, Otto.
- Crippled by your cowardice.
- Cowardice?
No. I'm crippled... by my memory.
You get your memories back
over years. Not me.
I get it all back as my brain forms.
In the womb.
Endless hours, days, weeks, months.
No room to move!
Nothing for my brain to do but eat itself.
All these lifetimes,
the magnitude of this gift,
and you haven't learned a thing.
I have to get out.
I have to make it stop.
Don't do it. Don't give him anything.
Where is treadway?
We storming the beach at normandy?
You never know with the artisan.
Let's get ready.
Color out, please.
So, the artisan's a gambler?
No, he's a hedonist.
Infinite lives,
infinite opportunity for debauchery.
Sounds like my kinda guy.
Alexa, music off.
Get him cleaned up and outta here.
You're operating on dead guys now?
Da Vinci used to cut into human cadavers
so that he could better understand
the human form.
For me...
I'm all about that brain, baby.
But you know that all too well.
Oh, what a beautiful cranial arch
you got this time around.
I could better examine it
if I severed your head from your neck.
Like treadway did to me when last we met.
- Try it.
- Oh.
Bathurst took the hub.
- Does he have the egg?
- No.
Think we'd be here if he did?
Wherever it is, it's still in his head.
Treadway?
So they say.
Wait. Is he blocked?
Well, well, well, look at this.
Huh.
So... your hard drive got fragged,
which means we're gonna
have to reset your memory.
And, Heinrich, I gotta tell ya,
I'm really gonna enjoy this.
Check this out.
You're all familiar with the idea
that when you die,
your life flashes before your eyes, right?
This machine enhances that experience,
prolonging your sense of time,
allowing you to restore
or reorder everything inside.
This... this right here
is the closest you're gonna get
to a total mental reboot.
Are you planning on trying to drown me?
'Cause I got a thing about drowning.
- Which is?
- I don't like it!
What kind of success rate
is this guy working with anyway?
Confidence is... high.
Yeah, and so are you, obviously.
Okay. Hey.
I like you this time around.
You're actually funny.
Don't take this the wrong way,
but you're usually kind of a jerk.
- It's true.
- Yeah, she gets it.
- So, I'm supposed to trust this guy?
- I wouldn't.
First, I resent the gender labeling.
Second, you can trust
that we share the same goal.
Really? Which is?
Bathurst wants to what,
destroy every living thing on earth?
Well, that's gonna ruin
a pretty great party
I've got goin' on here.
This guy's out of his mind. Hey...
There's a reason
you didn't bring me here before.
- I could die in there.
- Yeah.
Could it work?
It could.
But you have a choice, Evan.
No, I don't have a choice.
I... I can't let anybody else get hurt
because of what's in my head.
All right. Leap-of-faith time.
Let's just do it now
before I change my mind. All right?
Let's go. Turn your machine on.
Ooh. Ready to go for a swim?
- Yes. This is gonna be so fun!
- Just shut up and turn it on.
Prolongs your sense of t/me.
Whatever happens,
don't let them stop until it's done.
He'll hold his breath
as long as he can, and then...
Base instinct takes over.
Twenty-two. Too many.
Twenty. No more. And 18.
Oh, my god. He's drowning.
That's the whole idea.
- Maybe we should pull him out.
- He's not there yet. Two more minutes.
Abel, listen to me. If I fail...
Come on.
Nora...
He's dying.
We're close. We are close.
Doesn't have a pulse!
Get him out!
Come on! Come on.
Okay. Okay.
Get out of the way.
Come on.
He's gone.
We killed him.
If / fa/I, look inside.
Evan, you're okay. Just breathe.
I am treadway. I am treadway.
Hey. Whoa, whoa.
I'm treadway.
If you are treadway, answer this.
Do you know where the egg is?
Yes.
- Yes?
- Yes.
Look inside. Look inside.
We were trained to think of bodies
as unimportant, right?
- Right.
- Just shells meant to be discarded.
Well, treadway knew the one place...
That nobody would look.
Abel? Abel, listen to me.
If I fail, look inside.
It's in his body.
Back at the hub.
It's been there the whole time. Come on.
I am shocked that that worked.
I knew it was you the whole time.
That's why I let you win.
Oh, you let me, huh?
Whoo! I don't know about you guys,
but I could use a drink.
Come on, we don't have time for...
Security lockdown!
- I'm hit.
- You all right?
Hey! Follow me.
- Come on. We gotta go.
- Open emergency lift.
- We gotta go. We gotta go.
- Wait!
Are you crazy? They're about to breach!
We're not running, all right?
I'm tired of running.
- I'm gonna fight 'em right now.
- Hang in there, trace.
She's dead.
Oh, sh...
Guys, we need to leave now.
- I'm staying.
- What?
We stay here, we fight 'em now.
- You're leaking like the Titanic.
- I'm fine.
If you die here, who stops bathurst?
He's right.
Hey.
You make this worth it, dziecko.
Then buy me some time.
Open weapons room door.
Good luck.
Careful, sir.
Oh, I will be.
We're taking treadway's body to Scotland.
Very well.
Keep him alive.
I'll do the best I can,
but he's lost a lot of blood.
The keys are in the car.
Heinrich.
Good of you to join us.
I only wish you were here to see this...
To understand your...
Your role in this.
The end of all our debates.
The end of all things.
Have it cleaned and tested.
Make sure it's the real thing.
Is it really over?
Not quite yet.
Never underestimate treadway.
You're awake.
Where am I?
I told Nora I'd wait with you
until you woke up.
You're in my safe house.
- What are you doing?
- I'm doing your morphine!
- Where is she?
- Huh? Oh, she went after bathurst.
Oh, shit.
She's not doing this alone. No way.
Whoa, whoa! Come on, man.
You try running out now, you'll bleed out
before you reach the compound.
If we're going down,
we're going down together.
Hey, hey. Hey, hey.
I just patched you up, man.
Let me catch you up
on the current situation.
If bathurst gets his way, we're all done.
There's no more second chances.
I'm gonna get the egg and kill him.
She told me you were one of us.
Obviously, you're just full of shit.
Diagnostics are done.
The bomb is ready for the egg.
Have them load it on the plane.
Come here, you bastard.
Do you think he'll...
Let us do this?
The end of all things.
Move, move, move! On the rig! Let's go!
Move, move!
Dropping in three, two, one.
- Do you need a ride?
- Love one.
- You okay?
- No. Don't ask.
Did you see that?
Nora, you okay?
Okay, come on.
I got you.
I'll get you out of here. Come on.
Oh, shit.
You all right? Oh, shit.
Hey. We gotta get you out of here.
- You gonna be okay to move?
- Yeah, I'll be fine.
Okay. Come on.
- You gotta go.
- Bathurst is getting away.
His hard drives are here.
I have to destroy them and free them all.
I'll see you again.
We'll be landing in Glasgow
in 16 minutes, sir.
Stay low.
Use tfr.
Oh, my god.
Come on. Come on.
They're all here.
All the souls.
We have to free them all.
Nora. Nora, hey. Hey.
Stay with me, okay? We are so close.
Let's blow some shit up, huh?
Shit!
We've lost engine three, sir.
We're gonna have to land the aircraft.
What the hell are you doing? Sir!
Please. You're gonna crash
the aircraft. Sir!
It's impossible.
I-Impossible.
He's opened the bloody top hatch, sir.
You disappoint me.
No recognition whatsoever, huh?
I think I should feel hurt.
Car crash? Steel plate, remember?
Treadway, you can't deactivate it!
It's happening!
Death isn't the end. Not for us.
Maybe not for any of us.
New chapter, same story.
I can carry you out.
No way.
I'll free them.
Here.
- I'll see you around.
- Yeah.
I'll find you in the beginn/ng.
I love you.
I ask myself ..
What did being Evan ll/lccau/e y teach me?
If each new life is a chance
to build on what was,
a chance to press forward
to the best of what could be...
Go, go, go!
Why will some of us have to pick up
the sword and fight aga/n...
Wh/le others discover a new beginn/ng?
Nora?
It's hope. That's whatl learned
yes, we fall. Yes, we fa/I.
Yes, sometimes we screw up
everything we touch.
But each moment we live
is connected by a belief
that the actions we take
will next day, next week, next life
add up to something more,
something bigger than yourself
And next... well, the possrbil/ties are...
Infinite.
When your son starts asking questions
about his past,
give me a call.
He says he's just a child.
What about your sword?
That's not my sword. It's his.
Artisan, what took you so long?
See you soon, treadway.