Long time no see, Okkotsu.
Don't come near me.
Oh, come on, don't be so cold.
I said don't.
Do you know how much
I've wanted to slug you?
Just imagine how I've felt.
Right?
Stop it.
If you keep me on edge like this,
I might just kill you.
Don't come near me!
Rika-chan!
Huh? Rika?
Record: November 2016, Tokyo
Due to persistent bullying by classmates,
four male students, including the leader, suffered grave injuries.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry...
A complete cover-up and a secret execution?
That's ridiculous.
The boy in question consented, though.
He's underage.
Just a 16-year-old child.
We also don't know how
many he'd curse to death.
He's already turned the tables
on three grade 2 sorcerers
and a grade 1 sorcerer.
That's why you've turned to me.
Have you forgotten that?
Then you're actually...
Yes.
Okkotsu Yuta...
will be taken to Jujutsu High.
What is this,
Okkotsu Yuta-kun?
It used to be a knife.
I tried to die,
but Rika-chan interfered.
That's dark.
You're starting at a new school today.
I'm not going.
I don't want to hurt anyone anymore,
so I'm not going outside anymore.
But...
living by yourself gets lonely.
The curse placed upon you
is one that can save people, too,
depending on how it's used.
Tokyo
Jujutsu High School
Learn how to use that power.
It's not like it'll be too late
to cast everything away after that.
JUJUTSU KAISEN
Did you hear about the
transfer student coming today?
They say he "stuffed" four of
his classmates into a locker.
He killed them?
Tuna mayo?
No, but gravely injured, apparently.
Hmm... Well, if he's cocky, I'll wring him out.
Bonito flakes.
I'll now... be introducing...
the transfer student!
Everyone, get excited!
Get excited.
I heard he's an awfully sour one.
I'm not going to create the mood
for someone like that.
Salmon.
Oh, well.
Come on in!
I sense a really damp mood in there.
I'll ignore him.
Wha?!
I'm Okkotsu Yut—
Is this some kind of test?
Hey.
You're cursed.
This is a place to learn curses.
It's not a place for the cursed to be.
Huh?
The number of people that die
mysterious deaths or go missing
in Japan is over 10,000 a year on average.
Most of those are casualties of curses
born from the negative emotions of people.
Among them are also malicious
cases caused by curse users.
Only curses can affect other curses.
This where we learn curses
to exorcise curses:
Tokyo Jujutsu High School.
Tell me that ahead of time!
He just now told him that?!
Sorry.
Oh, you all should back away quickly.
Do not...
Wait! Rika-chan!
...bully Yuta!
Special-Grade Cursed Human Okkotsu Yuta
Special-Grade Cursed Apparition Orimoto Rika
Record: Six Years Ago, Sendai City, Miyagi Prefecture
Over there, over there!
What is it?
Happy birthday, Yuta.
Yay! Can I open it?
Go ahead.
Huh? I can open it?!
I said go ahead.
Wow!
Huh? A ring?
An engagement ring.
Engagement?
It's a promise.
That when we both grow up,
we'll get married.
Is this real?!
Hey!
Hey! Call an ambulance!
Idiot! Look at her!
Are they okay?
There's no saving her!
What happened?
Her head's crushed in!
But still...
A child got run over by a car! Yes! Hurry!
Help them!
I can't go near that!
Rika-chan?
Yuta...
Yuta.
When we grow up,
we'll get married!
It's a promise.
So as you can see,
this is the boy cursed by Rika-chan,
who just loves him...
Okkotsu Yuta-kun!
Be nice to him, everyone!
If you attack Yuta, Rika-chan's
curse will activate... or not.
Either way, be careful, everyone.
Say that sooner.
These guys are being all rebellious,
so I'll introduce them quick-like.
I have a feeling this teacher is the problem.
This is the cursed tool user, Zen'in Maki.
She uses special tools to exorcise curses.
This is the cursed
speech user, Inumaki Toge.
He can only speak in rice ball ingredients,
so good luck conversing.
Kelp.
This is Panda.
I'm Panda. Nice to meet you.
Well, there you have it.
He didn't give me the
explanation I wanted most!
Okay, now there are four first-years!
Three and one animal.
For your afternoon jujutsu practice,
you'll be in pairs of two on two.
Toge, Panda, pair up.
Let's do our best.
Maki, Yuta, pair up.
Geh!
She just voiced disgust?!
U-Um, I-I hope we can work together.
You were bullied, weren't you?
Bull's-eye, huh?
I totally get it. Even I'd bully you.
Maybe it's because of your curse?
It's written on your face that you're
branding yourself as a good person.
It's sickening.
Why are you acting like the victim
when you're being protected?
You've been passive your
whole life, haven't you?
Jujutsu High isn't so easy that
you can get by without any goal.
Maki!
That's enough!
Bonito flakes.
Okay, fine. Get off my case.
Sorry about her.
She has a habit of acting
like she understands others.
No...
She's right.
Where are we?
It's just an elementary school.
Huh?
Just an elementary school where
some children have gone missing.
Missing?!
It happens in places like this.
It's probably the work of
a naturally-occurring curse.
You're saying the kids
were kidnapped by a curse?
Yup.
Two so far.
Curses tend to settle in spots
that many people have memories of.
Schools, hospitals...
Places often remembered with negative
emotions are a receptacle for them.
As those emotions build up,
they cause a curse to be born,
like it was here.
We're here to exorcise the curse
and save the children,
or if they're dead, retrieve them.
Huh? Dead?
Emerge from darkness, blacker than darkness.
Purify that which is impure.
It's turning into night?
It's a veil.
It's a barrier that will smoke out the curse
and keep you all from
being seen by those outside.
It's easy to undo from inside.
Now, do be careful...
not to die.
D-Die? Sensei?!
Transfer student.
Don't get distracted.
Put... me... on?
Put me on?
I-It's coming this way!
Wh-Wh-What do we do?!
Don't scream.
Remember this.
The weaker curses are,
the more they group together.
Of course, the same could be said for humans.
Incredible...
Just one blow...
Come on, let's move it.
Huh? Where to?
Inside, obviously.
Zen'in-san, aren't you scared?
Don't use my last name.
S-Sorry...
But it really seems like
ghosts would be here.
Though we've already seen some.
There aren't many curses here,
even though the veil's been drawn.
No, they're here, just not attacking.
Is it because he's here?
Something just moved!
Hey!
Yes?!
What grade are you?
Huh? In English proficiency?
Jujutsu sorcerers are ranked
in grades from 4 to 1.
But I only just came to Jujutsu High.
I don't think I have that.
Ugh, forget it.
Show me your student ID.
You got one from that
dumb blindfolded guy, right?
Dumb blindfolded guy?
Yes, here you go.
Well, if you joined with no prior history,
you're probably grade 4...
Tokyo Jujutsu High School              [Student ID]
Special
Student ID #
Name         Okkotsu Yuta
DOB: 03/07/2001
This is proof that the individual listed above is a student.
Special-grade?!
Special-grade is above
even grade 1, isn't it?
This sounds like it has to be a joke!
Zen'in-san!
Zen'in-san! Zen'in-san!
Behind you.
Shit!
You're way too damn big!
You bastard!
Thank, thank, thank you for the meal!
Shit! Shit!
I dropped my cursed tool!
Let us out, damn it!
Where are we?
We're in that curse's stomach!
You shouldn't be passing out over this.
You mean it ate us?!
That's right!
I thought you were being
protected by your curse?!
Even I don't know what
makes Rika-chan come out!
More importantly, what do we do now?!
After time passes and the veil
goes away, help will come for us.
This is embarrassing! Shit!
Help!
Huh?
Please! He's about to die!
You're saying the kids
were kidnapped by a curse?
Yup.
Two so far.
We're here to exorcise the curse
and save the children,
or if they're dead, retrieve them.
Thank goodness they're alive.
No, it's not good.
Look closer.
The big one's obviously been
affected by the curse, too.
Both of them could die at any minute.
Oh, no...
What do we do?!
There's nothing we can do!
We can only wait for help!
Not everyone has a resistance
to curses like you do!
Zen'in-san?
Zen'in-san?!
What's this wound?
Are you cursed?
Is she going to die?
Please, save us, mister!
Please!
You keep asking, but I can't—
Okkotsu!
Seriously, why did you come
to Jujutsu High?!
What do you want to do?!
What do you want to have?!
What do you want to achieve?!
I... don't want anyone to get hurt anymore.
I tried to lock myself away and disappear.
But I was told it's
lonely being all by myself,
and I couldn't argue.
I want to interact with someone!
I want to be needed by someone!
I want the confidence to
say it's okay that I'm alive!
Then exorcise them.
Exorcise curses, exorcise them,
exorcise them over and over!
Confidence and friends will
all come to you after that!
That's the kind of place Jujutsu High is!
Rika-chan.
What?
Lend me your strength.
Who are you?
Be quiet!
Now that's terrifying.
So this is the full picture of Orimoto Rika,
the special-grade cursed apparition?
So scary.
Wow!
So pretty!
I'm so pretty!
I love it!
Everyone...
It's just a little further!
I need to get Sensei to check them all soon,
while Rika-chan's distracting the curses!
I can't collapse yet!
Not yet!
I just decided I was going
to change, here and now!
You can do it,
Yuta.
Yeah, I will!
Welcome back.
You did well.
They say both Maki and the kids will be fine.
Thank goodness.
You don't look very satisfied.
I managed to call Rika-chan
out myself for the first time.
Really? That's a step forward.
One, two...
Stop, Yuta!
I said stop!
Stop, Rika-chan!
There! Take that!
It's a promise.
When we both grow up, we'll get married.
Sure!
Then we'll be together forever and ever!
What's wrong?
Nothing...
Just remembering something.
I don't think Rika-chan cursed me.
I think I might have cursed Rika-chan.
This is my personal theory,
but there's no curse more twisted than love.
Sensei.
While I'm at Jujutsu High,
I'll break Rika-chan's curse.
The special-grade cursed
apparition, Orimoto Rika,
was fully manifested for 422 seconds.
We entrusted you with Okkotsu
precisely to prevent this sort of thing.
There's no room for excuses,
Gojo Satoru.
Well, I never planned on making any excuses.
How can you joke about this?!
If Orimoto Rika had remained out of control,
she could have wiped out an entire town!
I would have risked my life to stop her.
Listen, there's only one thing
we can say about that curse:
"I don't understand."
Why did a little girl who wasn't
from any line of jujutsu sorcerers
become such an immense curse?
We can't control something
we don't understand.
So it'll take trial and error.
Just leave it alone for a while.
Do not forget that Okkotsu's
secret execution was only suspended.
And don't you forget
that if it comes to that,
I'll side with Okkotsu.
Christ, damn rude geezers.
I don't ever want to become like them.
I'll have to be careful.
Besides,
no one's allowed to take
youth away from young people.
Maki, Toge, last lap.
No one is.
Well, go ahead.
S-Sure...
It's nearly impossible to exorcise
a curse as big as Orimoto Rika.
However, breaking it is a different story.
You have to read the thousands, maybe
tens of thousands, of knots of cursed energy,
and unravel them one by one.
It's a method that can only be pursued
by you, the one she's cursed.
What exactly do I do?
Use this.
A katana?
Curses are most stable when
they're possessing an object.
Back then, you used that ring
to connect to Orimoto Rika.
The pipeline's already there.
So now you need to borrow part of Rika's curse,
imbue it into the katana, and control it.
Increase the amount as you repeat it,
and eventually you'll have
all of it under your control.
Then you're free.
Both you and her.
Imbue the curse into the katana...
And at the same time...
You need to learn how to wield a blade!
You're super weak, after all.
First, we'll have to train you thoroughly.
Tuna.
Hey, hey, everyone!
How's it going?
Oh, uh...
Don't get distracted.
Right.
Take your stance already, idiot!
She's ruthless!
Right!
You're going to land a
blow on me, aren't you?
Yes!
She dodged that?!
But she's off-balance!
I'll get her on the landing!
No way!
There, you're dead.
I win again.
Was that last part necessary?
Don't be soft.
You should always treat
it like it's a real battle.
Pain or the lack thereof makes a
huge difference in how fast you grow.
That's right. I'm...
One more, please!
I'm going to break Rika-chan's curse!
It's been three months since
Yuta came to Jujutsu High.
His movements have gotten a lot better.
Salmon.
His personality is more positive now, too.
Salmon roe.
Maki looks like she's having fun, too.
Before now, she didn't get to spar
much with a fellow weapon—
Revelation!
Yuta! Hey, come here!
Come on!
Huh?
What's up, Panda-kun?
A super important discussion! Listen closely!
Do you prefer big boobs or small boobs?
Right now?!
I've never really given it much thought...
Sexy Talk
But I suppose I prefer them somewhat big?
Oh-ho?
Maki!
Huh?
You've got a chance!
Chance! Chance! Chance!
What crazy ideas are you getting?
I'll kill you!
Don't be so shy!
Are you an elementary schooler?
All right, I'll kill you!
I don't give a damn about CITES!
What's this about?
Kelp.
I still don't really understand Inumaki-kun,
so he's a little scary...
Okay, gather round!
You two, continue your training.
Toge, you've been requested.
It's a curse you're perfect for.
Go exorcise it quickly.
Salmon.
Requested?
Toge's the only grade 2
sorcerer among us first-years.
He's allowed to take missions on his own.
Wow, that's impressive.
You're a special-grade.
You go with him, Yuta.
You'll be Toge's support.
Huh? Support?
Well, more like an observer, really.
There's a wide variety of jujutsu,
so you can assume there are as many ways
to exorcise a curse as there are sorcerers.
Toge's cursed speech is one good example.
Make sure to learn from him.
Cursed speech?
As the term suggests,
it's imbuing speech with curses.
Well, it'll make sense once you see it.
To break a curse,
you must first understand curses.
My first real mission...
No, my second.
I'm so nervous!
Salmon.
Huh?!
Oh, I-I'm sorry...
Yuta, one second.
Yes?
Sorry, I won't be able to
supervise this time.
But the job is one Toge could
typically handle on his own,
so you can take it easy.
There's only one thing
you need to be careful of.
Don't let Rika out.
There's no guarantee she'll go back
in like she luckily did last time.
Only use what power of Rika's
that you can imbue in your sword.
If you let her out fully again...
If I let her out?
You and I will both be killed!
Counting on you.
Wha...
Why does he have to rub salt
in that wound right now?!
We've arrived.
Every Tues/Fri get a 5x Point Bonus!
Hapina Shopping District.
At this time, most of the
shutters here are closed.
Authorized Personnel Only
No Trespassing
We're
closed.
"There's a project to demolish the entire
area and attract a shopping mall."
"During an inspection of the area,
we confirmed a pack of low-level curses."
"We'd like to request that the grade 2
sorcerer, Inumaki, exorcise them."
Huh? Wait, where's sorcerer Inumaki?
Not here?
Thank you.
Oh, Ijichi-san, over there.
He was shopping?
What did you buy?
Throat Remedy
Throat medicine?
In short, it would cause all
kinds of issues down the road
if the building they're spending so
much money on developed a bad history,
so they want us to exorcise it now.
Salmon.
Now, I'll draw the veil.
Good luck.
He said it was a pack of low-level curses.
Pollack roe.
Danger!
That's not fair, Mama.
Onii-chan got more.
So what? Let's trade doubles.
I smell olives.
I want to eat sushi!
Reporting a lost child.
Cheap stuff! Cheap stuff!
It's not scary if you cross with everyone.
The weaker curses are,
the more they group together.
Even so, there's just too many of them!
Inumaki-kun?!
It's dangerous if you get that clo—
Explode.
This is cursed speech?
Huh? Oh... It's over already?
Tuna mayo.
His voice is really worn out!
Oh, that explains the throat medicine.
That's an incredible power,
but it comes with a good deal of risk, too.
Bonito flakes...
What's wrong?
Huh? You're right.
The veil isn't lifting.
Huh?
We won't be able to get out.
What is this curse? Its presence is
nothing like the ones from before...
Zomba.
Inumaki-kun!
Twist!
What, what, what?! What is that?!
That curse...
He said they'd be low-level!
This isn't what we were told!
There's that thing's size, too.
It's way scarier than the big guys
from the elementary school.
That's right!
Inumaki-kun, you're hurt.
Is your finger all right?
Wow, that looks painful.
Salmon.
You shouldn't mess with it!
Sorry.
It's my fault.
It doesn't seem to be pursuing
us or searching for us.
I'll contact Ijichi-san.
No Service
Enter Your Passcode
Out of service?
But why?
Bonito flakes.
Huh?
Because of the veil?
If the veil won't lift,
then we have to exorcise it, right?
Inumaki-kun?
Should you be moving around already?
Kelp.
You're going to go alone?
Thank you, Inumaki-kun.
But I'm all right.
Let's both do our best together!
Oh?
Get him, Yuta!
It's mad?! Why?!
It was already scary enough!
Don't take your eyes off him.
Don't stop moving.
Imbue the curse into the katana.
Inumaki-kun is kind.
He doesn't want to
accidentally curse others,
so he speaks in rice ball components—
words that can't carry curses.
Even today, he helped me out.
He tried to keep me away from danger.
Even back then,
he was showing consideration
for my anxiety, wasn't he?
Zora.
That was shallow!
And he's tough!
I still can't compete with this curse, but...
Inumaki-kun!
I'll make sure to respond
to Inumaki-kun's kindness!
Get crushed!
Wow!
Mustard leaf!
Oh, I'm fine.
It's only a scratch.
Salmon.
Yeah, good work!
Once I break Rika-chan's curse,
I'll be a normal person.
I won't be able to stay
at Jujutsu High anymore,
but until then,
I want to be useful to everyone.
Oh, what do we do about the veil?
What a shame.
I came here to see this rumored Rika-chan.
As a fellow special-grade,
I was hoping to meet her soon.
Tokyo Jujutsu High School                [Student ID]
Special
Student ID #
Name            Okkotsu Yuta
DOB: 03/07/2001
This is proof that the individual listed above is a student.
I needed to deliver
something he dropped, too.
Toge's cursed speech
is something he's been able
to use since he was born,
so back in the day, he struggled quite a bit.
Sometimes he cursed people
he never intended to curse.
His situation was rather similar to yours.
That's why he's been worried about you
since the day you transferred in.
It's easy to misunderstand him,
but he's a good guy.
I hope you'll be kind to him.
Yeah, I'll—
Come on, let's start morning training!
Oh, right.
Panda! What are you laughing about?!
I'll kill you!
Huh? It's nothing, though.
Maki-san, hey...
I'd like to imbue my curse
into my katana more smoothly.
Do you know any tricks?
Nope.
Don't ask me about cursed energy.
I scoured every inch
of the shopping district,
and I found three different
types of residuals.
Even Ijichi-san said we weren't likely
to find any more than that.
Okay, got it. Thanks.
You bet!
My apologies.
Our inspection showed that someone
lowered a second veil on top of my own.
In addition,
a semi-first-grade curse made
an unexpected appearance.
It's my fault for not being more thorough.
I'll accept any punishment.
No, you're fine. You were just outclassed.
Meaning?
Do you have an idea who did it?
Death to Fools
Punishment to the Weak
Love to the Strong
Geto Suguru.
One of the four special-grade jujutsu sorcerers,
who was banished from Jujutsu High
after cursing over a hundred
normal people to death.
He's the worst curse user.
Death to
Punishment to
Love to
Really, I'll be fine. Let's go home now.
It's all right. Just wait a little longer.
But...
So, you said your daughter
was being haunted by a ghost.
Isn't that right, Sato-san?
Ah, yes... um... it's Saito, though...
No, you are Sato-san.
That's what I've decided,
so Sato is better.
Uh-huh...
Mom, let's go home.
But you haven't been able
to sleep lately, right?
This is so shady, though.
You constantly feel
a piercing gaze upon you.
Sometimes your shoulders feel heavy,
and it gets hard to breathe, doesn't it?
Almost as if you've forgotten how to breathe.
And you often
dream of being raped.
How did you know that?
Don't move.
Huh? No way... I feel much better!
Honestly, I don't know how
we could ever repay you.
Oh, no, we should all help
each other in times of need.
Please rely on me anytime you need to.
See, I told you he was simply godly!
Yeah.
Godly, huh?
You're a smart one, aren't you?
Filthy monkey who can't even use jujutsu.
Your true feelings are showing, Geto-sama.
The leaders have all gathered
in the meeting room.
What are you doing?
It's disinfecting deodorant.
I don't want everyone to
catch the monkey smell.
I'm so happy.
How long has it been since we all gathered?
I know. Let's take a photo together
since we're all here.
Where'd I put my single-lens?
Right here.
Geto! Give me Geto!
Geto! Damn you!
Well, if it isn't Kanemori-san.
What brings you here in such a panic?
Don't play dumb!
Hurry up and exorcise my curse!
Do you know how much I've paid you?!
How much?
Roughly one hundred and five million yen.
But there have been no donations
for the past six months.
Well—
Ah... I guess that's it for you.
What are you sayi—
All monkeys have their own role.
There are money-collecting monkeys
and curse-collecting monkeys.
You're the former.
If you're out of money,
I have no further use for you.
Screw you!
Suck, suck... Suck, suck...
Suck, suck, suck, suck...
Disgusting.
Are they really the same species?
That's why I'm always saying
they're monkeys.
The time is right, my family.
Let's lower the curtain
on the age of monkeys
and build a paradise for jujutsu sorcerers.
First, we must fell the
cornerstone of the jujutsu world,
Jujutsu High.
What's the matter, Yuta?
Uh, well... I just had a bad premonition.
You're imagining things.
Yep, imagining things.
Bonito flakes.
Huh?
Guys, wait...
Well, your ability to sense
cursed energy sucks, you know.
Figures it'd be dulled, with something
like Rika constantly with you.
Tuna.
We still aren't picking up on
any actions from Geto.
Are you sure you're not worried over nothing?
Principal, I'm sad to say that's not possible.
I confirmed it myself on the scene.
There's no way I would mistake
the residuals of Suguru's cursed energy.
Suguru...
God damn it!
Speak of the devil!
Gather all sorcerers on campus, semi-first-grade
and above, in the circle out front!
That's unusual.
Yuta's intuition was correct.
Salmon.
You're... not staff.
I haven't seen that curse before.
Salmon roe.
Wow, big bird!
This place never changes.
Yuck! Geto-sama, is this really Tokyo?
Feels like the sticks.
Nanako, that's rude.
What? But don't you think so, too, Mimiko?
Come on! Get off already!
Aren't you cold?
Who are they?
Whoa, it's a panda!
How cute!
And who are all of you?
Intruders aren't allowed in, by Yuta-san here.
Kelp!
Huh?
Go home before you get beaten!
By Yuta-san!
Huh?!
Nice to meet you, Okkotsu-kun.
I'm Geto Suguru.
He's fast!
Huh? Oh... Nice to meet you...
You possess a truly wonderful power, I see.
I believe that
great power ought to be used toward great ends.
Have you ever questioned
the current state of the world?
This world where jujutsu
sorcerers act in secret
in order to protect the order
of commonplace society.
You see, there's this established paradox
saying the strong must accommodate the weak.
It's so deplorable!
Uh-huh...
The apex of all creation has
halted its own path of evolution!
It's nonsense!
It's high time mankind reconsidered
its strategy for survival!
Which is why we'd like you to help us.
Help with what?
We're going to kill all non-sorcerers
and create a world
with only jujutsu sorcerers.
What...
...is he saying?
Could you stop preaching your
crazy beliefs to my students?
Satoru! Long time no see!
First of all, get away from those kids, Suguru.
I had heard this year's first-years
were all outstanding students.
Now I understand.
It was all your doing.
A special-grade cursed human,
a cursed corpse mutation,
the descendant of the cursed speech users,
and...
the Zen'in clan's failure.
You piece of...
Watch what you say.
Because I don't need any
monkeys like you in my world.
I'm sorry.
I don't really understand
what you're talking about,
but...
I can't help anyone who insults my friends!
My apologies. It wasn't
my intention to upset you.
Then what exactly did you come for?
To declare war.
Everyone gathered here,
open your ears and listen closely!
On the coming December 24th,
when the sun sets,
we shall conduct the Night
Parade of a Hundred Demons.
It will take place in the crucible of curses,
Shinjuku, Tokyo...
Kabuki Town, First Street
and the holy land of jujutsu,
Kyoto.
We will unleash a thousand
curses upon each place.
And of course, their command will be "massacre."
If you wish to avoid a scene straight out of hell,
come and stop it with all your might.
Let us freely
curse each other!
Geto-sama!
The store's gonna close!
It's already that late?
I'm sorry, Satoru.
These girls just insist on getting
crêpes from Takeshita Street.
Hurry!
So I'll be taking my leave.
Good grief. I don't see what's so good
about a place with so many monkeys.
Did you think we'd just let you leave?
You don't want to do that.
Your precious students are within my range.
Well, everyone, see you on the battlefield.
Survival of the weakest.
That's the proper form society should take.
It should help the weak
and discourage the strong.
Listen, Satoru.
Sorcerers exist to protect non-sorcerers.
That's your argument?
I hate righteousness.
Are you the strongest
because you're Gojo Satoru?
Or are you Gojo Satoru
because you're the strongest?
What are you trying to say?
If I could become you,
then wouldn't my foolish ideals
become reasonable possibilities?
I've decided how to live my life.
All that's left is to do what I can
to the best of my ability.
Geto Suguru.
A special-grade curse user who
uses cursed spirit manipulation.
He's able to draw in and manipulate
naturally occurring, unbound curses.
It seems he's established a religious group
to collect curses from its followers.
He should still have the curses
he previously possessed,
and considering the declining trend in the
number of curses reported in recent years...
His claim to possess
2,000 may not be a bluff.
Even so, statistically, most of them
have to be weaklings at grade 2 or below.
Even with a generous estimate,
there can't be much more than 50 curse users.
That's actually the scary part.
I find it hard to believe he'd
start a war he couldn't win.
God damn!
Put out a call for aid to all alumni,
the three major clans, and even the Ainu Jujutsu Society.
It's all-out war!
This time, that curse, Geto, will be completely
exorcised!
That's what that muscle-brained principal
is probably spouting right now.
December 24th, Day of the Night Parade of a Hundred Demons
If we seriously tried to kill each other,
our chance of success would be about 30%.
If the Jujutsu Society joins in as well,
we'll barely have a 20% chance.
However,
there's just one move that makes
that slim chance of victory
jump straight to 99%.
I kill Okkotsu Yuta and obtain the special-grade
cursed apparition, Orimoto Rika.
They still naïvely believe
my bluff from my time in school.
It doesn't matter if
the cursed spirit is bound.
So long as I kill its master,
I can absorb any curse I want.
With such high odds of victory,
the school won't use Okkotsu
as one of their cards.
After all, there's a chance he could
wipe out both enemies and allies.
The true purpose of the
Night Parade of a Hundred Demons
is to get Okkotsu isolated and unprotected.
Now, let's raise the curtain on a new age.
It sounds like...
something crazy is going down.
Maki-san!
What are you doing here?
Classes are canceled for the week.
Well, I just felt kinda restless.
No one in the dorms is around, either.
That's because the second-years
were dispatched to Kyoto earlier.
Toge and the third- and fourth-years
are in Shinjuku as backup.
The principal really likes Panda, too,
so he's probably with Toge.
I see.
Ask.
Huh?
You've been curious, right?
About why I'm a "failure."
Well, um... yes.
My family, the Zen'in clan,
is one of the elite families of jujutsu
sorcerers known as the three major clans.
Do you know what the minimum requirement
to be a jujutsu sorcerer is?
Huh? What is it?
It's being able to see curses.
Oh, right.
Ordinary people can sometimes see them
in special circumstances, like at death's door,
but I can't see curses
without these lame glasses.
The cursed tools I use are already
imbued with cursed energy.
It doesn't come from me.
Though, thanks to that,
I got out of that family.
The food was awful, the rooms were small,
and it was crawling with old men I didn't know.
It seriously sucked!
Don't use my last name.
Not everyone has a resistance
to curses like you do!
Don't ask me about cursed energy.
Why are you still a jujutsu sorcerer, then?
Because I'm spiteful.
I'm going to make that family cry
when I return to them
as a grade 1 sorcerer who can't see curses!
Then I'll crush the Zen'in clan from within!
What?
Oh, I was just thinking that's so like you.
I wish...
I could be like you.
I wish I could be so strong and unyielding.
I wish I had never given birth to you.
You're the shame of the Zen'in clan!
Everyone,
you don't want to turn out like Maki.
If there's ever anything
I can help with, just ask.
Let's crush the Zen'in clan! Or something.
Moron. There's no point
if I don't do it by myself.
I'm going back to my room.
Okay. Later.
Am I an idiot?
Don't start thinking this
means you've been accepted!
Emerge from darkness, blacker than darkness.
Purify that which is impure.
A veil was drawn over the school?
But who... and why?
Keep the destruction of buildings
and infrastructure to a minimum.
There's a chance some civilians
still haven't evacuated.
If you find any, evacuate them.
Are you listening, Satoru?
There's one guy who looks like trouble.
I see. That bandaged guy.
Yes. We'll take on the rest.
I've said this many times, but...
I know.
We're only stalling them, right?
Let's just take it easy and have
some fun until Geto finishes his job.
You're here?
Is it a problem if I am?
What the hell are you doing here?
Sorry, but I don't have time
to chat with monkeys.
Gojo-san!
I have a report!
What's the matter?
Well...
That guy loves to show off,
and he's not on the front lines?
Is he in Kyoto?
We should have received
some kind of word if he was.
It's nothing. What's up?
I know this isn't the best time,
but I thought it wise to speak up sooner.
It's about the investigation into Okkotsu-kun
that you previously requested.
Panda! Toge!
What is—
No questions!
I'm sending you two to
Jujutsu High right now!
Huh?!
Geto is there now.
I'm absolutely, probably, certain!
Which is it?!
If my intuition is right,
in the worst case,
Yuta and Maki could both die!
I'll head there right after
I take care of that foreigner.
Protect those two.
Sorry, but defend them with your lives!
Right!
Salmon!
No way... They figured it out?
This is why I said you should
at least prepare a stand-in.
A bad dummy would only make things worse.
That's what Geto-sama said.
Mimiko, Nanako!
What?
We're stepping up the plan. Engage.
I've been waiting for this!
I'm your opponent,
special-grade.
Sorry,
but I'm in a hurry right now.
A veil's been drawn!
Does that mean Satoru's intuition was right?
I'll break the veil!
Then we'll take the shortest route!
Pollack roe!
Oh?
Someone made a hole in the veil.
Nothing ever goes quite as planned.
Should take them five minutes
from the point of entry to here.
Should I ignore them,
or should I take care of them?
It's so hard to decide.
They broke through all the walls
to take the shortest route?
Not bad.
Maki!
Focus.
This guy can handle close combat, too?
Oh?
Predictable.
Because it was a feint.
Drumming Beat!
That was close.
Same to you.
Plummet!
Toge! You okay?
Caviar.
Yeah, Maki comes first.
Maki, are you okay?
Maki?
Mustard leaf.
N-Not yet...
Huh?
Another quake?
I wonder what's going on.
Wonderful.
Wonderful!
I am incredibly touched right now!
You all raced here to save Okkotsu, right?
Jujutsu sorcerers are sacrificing
themselves for a fellow sorcerer!
Affection! Admiration!
The world I long for
is here before my eyes!
Maki-san?
To be honest,
I wanted you to live, too, Okkotsu.
But this is all for the
future of the jujutsu world.
Panda-kun...
Yuta...
Inumaki-kun...
Run... away...
Record: December 24th, 2017
Come out, Rika!
Special-Grade Cursed Apparition, Orimoto Rika
Fully Manifested a Second Time
I will kill you.
I'll murder you!
Quantity before quality.
What's your move, Queen of Curses?
Rika.
These three are horribly wounded,
especially Maki-san.
I won't let you die!
Not fair, not fair!
It's always you, always you!
What are you doing, Rika?
Huh?
That woman saved me.
Handle her with more care
than a butterfly or a flower!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
Don't be mad.
I'm not mad.
Don't hate me.
I don't hate you.
Our enemy is that man there.
Yuta, do you hate him?
Yeah, I loathe him.
Then I hate him, too!
Welcome back.
Why did you stop attacking?
Healing with cursed energy requires
an advanced reverse cursed technique.
It was more advantageous to let you
divide your attention over there.
Now, shall we start where we left off?
Rika, we're doing that.
Snake Eyes and Fangs?
Those are...
The cursed seals of the Inumaki clan!
Die.
Wonderful!
Cursed speech is a powerful technique
passed down in the Inumaki clan,
yet this young man pulled it off with
less than a year of studying jujutsu!
That really is hard to use.
The cursed energy scatters,
and it's hard to aim.
Inumaki-kun is incredible.
So Orimoto Rika's true form
is ever-changing.
She's an endless bundle of cursed energy.
Yes.
My friends are amazing.
And you! You!
I want her even more.
I'll beat you to a pulp!
Why is Nanami-san in Kyoto?
I wanted him to see me shine!
Shut up!
Quit griping and fight!
There are still more coming!
Man, what a pain.
That makes fifty.
I've cleared the numbers
required for the incentive,
so now to work a little bit more
and aim for that full bonus.
How old are you two?
Fifteen.
You're still just children.
It's not too late for you to turn back.
You don't know right from wrong, do you?
Annoying!
Mimiko, doesn't he totally piss you off?
Shall we hang him, Nanako?
None of you know, do you?
Just how jujutsu sorcerers are treated out
in the damn sticks that aren't even on maps.
Right or wrong?
You all can enjoy that by yourselves.
The way Geto-sama puts it,
black is white, and white is black, too.
We both believe in the world he's envisioned.
Anyone who gets in his way...
...we'll hang!
Huh?!
Miguel?
What are you doing?!
Look, and figure it out!
You're tenacious.
That rope...
It has an unusual curse woven into it.
It's disrupting my techniques.
I barely have half left.
How many decades do you think it took
the sorcerers in my country
to weave this one rope?!
Like I care.
One second of my time will outmatch it.
That's all there is to it.
Dummy!
You're in my way.
Not good! Gojo-san's snapped!
So this is the Limitless
technique Geto mentioned.
It interferes on the atomic level,
controlling space-time with precise
manipulation of cursed energy.
And what makes that all possible
is the power of those eyes.
Just over twelve more
minutes until my quota.
I'll keep running for my life!
Wow!
Ouch!
That last round was dangerous.
I'll focus on hit-and-run.
I'll give everything I've got
to endure these last ten minutes.
If I die, I'm cursing you, Geto!
Ieri-san, please look at this one, too.
I will. Set him down over there.
Right!
What were you all doing?
It's all right.
Ieri-san will fix you up.
We're counting on you!
Sheesh.
You really forced a heap
of trouble on us, Geto.
It's your first time experiencing
such violent emotion,
and cursed energy is
filling your body, isn't it?
That heightening of physical prowess,
that sense of omnipotence...
Your senses must be sharpened, too.
The riff-raff are no match for you now.
I'll have to crush you myself.
Follow my lead, Rika.
Mankind stands at the top of the food chain,
yet they imagined the existence
of higher beings and called them gods.
Don't you find that strange?
Especially when we jujutsu
sorcerers exist without belief.
In the end, those monkeys
just want to avert their eyes from the
existence of those better than them.
Don't go saying childish crap
like you want to be a god!
You're missing the point,
Okkotsu.
What I long for isn't enlightenment.
It's a chosen people.
There are times when the strong are buried and
oppressed by the weak due to sheer numbers.
And I'm telling you that the audacity
of the monkeys who do that
makes me so sick I could vomit.
Yuta, Yuta...
It's all right. I'm used to it now.
Are we done debating?
He's even faster!
You shouldn't have done that.
When you imbue a curse like that
too abruptly, the vessel won't last.
Didn't Satoru teach you that?
You imbue curses bit by—
You're not bad.
I don't understand!
I don't know about any
sorcerers outside of this school,
so I don't know
if you're right or not!
But in order to remain with all my friends...
In order for me to believe
it's okay that I'm alive...
I have to kill you!
You're egotistical.
Still, self-affirmation, huh?
There's probably nothing more
important than that in life.
In which case, I'll also use
my full force to kill you.
I won't compromise on quality
or quantity anymore.
Did you know
there are only four people
crowned special-grade?
Among curses, there are sixteen.
This is one of them.
Special-grade potential apparition,
Tamamo-no-mae incarnate!
On top of that,
I'll combine the 4,461
curses I possess into one,
and strike you with it.
Cursed Spirit Manipulation, Supreme Art:
Maelstrom.
Nanami-san.
I'll take care of it.
New Shadow Style, Simple Domain!
Quick Draw!
Don't let your guard down, Miwa!
Mechamaru, above!
You, too.
Everyone, stay alert.
Kamo-kun.
Seven cursed spirits at two o'clock.
Roger that. Where did Todo go?
Oh, I think you'll see him soon.
Where have you been all this time, Todo—
Wh-What is that cursed energy?
That one's dangerous, Todo!
Don't rush in on your own!
Wait for back—
Starting at eight, the talk show's
Christmas live special will be
hosting Takada-chan!
I can't keep wasting any time here!
Todo!
Kamo-kun.
Another ten or more cursed spirits
are approaching from six o'clock.
Everyone, prepare to intercept them!
Jeez, there's no end to them.
When is this going to be over?
Okkotsu.
I'm truly glad I came to kill you
before you could fully wield Orimoto Rika.
It's a promise.
When we both grow up, we'll get married.
Sure.
Then we'll be together forever and ever!
Rika.
Yes?
Thank you for always protecting me.
Thank you for falling in love with me.
Could you lend me your power one last time?
I want to stop him.
I don't need anything else after that.
I'll give you my future,
my heart, my body, everything.
From now on, we'll truly be together forever.
I love you, Rika.
Shall we die together?
Yuta! Yuta!
I love, love, love you!
He's offering himself as a sacrifice to
release the limit on her cursed energy?!
So that's how you want it, womanizer?!
That's rude.
It's pure love.
Then I fight for justice!
Wonderful!
Absolutely wonderful!
Truly the power to change the world!
If I had Rika, there would be no need
to sneak around gathering curses.
Next time.
Next time, I'll obtain her!
You're late,
Satoru.
To think you'd be the one here at my end.
Is my family safe?
Every last one of them managed to escape.
The ones in Kyoto were
under your orders, too, right?
Yeah.
Unlike you, I'm a kind man.
You sent those two assuming
that I'd defeat them, didn't you?
To set Okkotsu off.
I trusted you.
Trusted that a man as principled as you wouldn't
kill off young sorcerers without a reason.
Trust, huh?
I didn't think I still had any of that left.
Return this for me, will you?
Was the elementary school your doing, too?
Yeah.
I can't believe you.
Do you have any last words?
No matter what anyone says,
I hate those monkeys.
But I never held any hatred
for those in Jujutsu High.
I just couldn't wear a
heartfelt smile in this world.
Suguru.
At least hit me with some curses at my end.
Hey! Hey!
Yuta! Yuta!
Hey!
Hey, Yuta! Are you okay?!
Mustard leaf.
Wake up, Yuta!
Oh, he's awake.
Everyone...
Your injuries...
Maki-san. Inumaki-kun.
Wait! Panda-kun, your arm isn't healed!
Chill out. We're all doing better
than you right now.
Unlike these other two,
my arm can be fixed later.
Thanks for saving us.
Salmon.
Yuta...
Sorry, Rika-chan.
I've kept you waiting.
What's the matter, Yuta?
Well, uh...
In exchange for borrowing her power,
um, I promised to go with Rika-chan.
What?!
Don't you know that means dying?!
What were you thinking, you idiot?!
Uh, well, I...
Huh?
Rika-chan?
Congratulations.
You managed to break the curse.
Who are you?
Your good-looking guy, Gojo Satoru-sensei!
I thought the theory Yuta came
up with sounded interesting,
so I requested an investigation
into their families.
The investigation of Rika's was
finished quite a long time ago,
but Yuta's was full of holes at best.
So then it came to light.
You're the descendant of Sugawara Michizane!
That makes us super distant relatives!
Suga?!
Yay! Yay! Yay! Yuta, yay!
Huh? Who?
One of Japan's three great apparitions!
He's a super bigshot sorcerer.
Tuna.
You were right, Yuta.
Rika didn't place a curse on you.
You placed a curse on Rika.
Rika-chan...
What do I do?! Is she going to die?!
I have to save her!
Don't die! Don't die!
Don't die! Don't die! Don't die!
That's right.
Back then, I rejected Rika-chan's death.
Now the one who placed
the curse has canceled the bond.
So long as the one who was cursed
doesn't seek any penalty,
it's fully broken now.
Of course, that much was obvious
after seeing her in that form.
It was all my fault, wasn't it?
I turned you into that form,
I hurt all those people,
and I nearly caused everyone to die
when Geto came after me!
It's all...
It's all my...
Yuta, thank you...
for giving me more time,
and letting me stay by your side.
These past six years,
I've been happier than I ever was while alive.
Bye-bye. Take care.
And don't come over here too soon, okay?
Okay.
See you later.
It's a bit late now,
but you weren't at fault
for the incident with Geto.
He would've come to Jujutsu High
whether you were there or not.
You think so?
Also, here.
Oh, my student ID.
You found it for me, Sensei?
No, not me.
My best friend.
The only one I had.
Come on, Yuta! How long are
you gonna keep us waiting?
Let's go!
Yeah.
Theatrical Release
JUJUTSU KAISEN
This is good.
Isn't it?
I used a spice called Royco.
That gives it a good flavor.
Royco is a magic powder that makes
everything taste Kenyan when you add it.
More importantly,
they really went home, right?
Yeah.
Good, then.
This really is good. It's like nikujaga.
Nikujaga?
Call it beef stew. Beef stew!
What's wrong?
What are you doing here?
Huh?
Sensei?
Hey. Long time no see.