♪ I'm just a poor
Wayfaring stranger ♪
♪ Traveling through
A world of woe ♪
♪ Ain't no sickness
No toil, nor danger ♪
♪ In that bright land
To which I go ♪
♪ I'm going there
To see my father ♪
♪ I'm only going over Jordan
I'm only going over home ♪
♪ I know dark clouds
Gonna gather 'round me ♪
♪ I know my way
Is rough and steep ♪
♪ I'm only going over Jordan ♪
♪ I'm only going over home ♪
Stop it.
Stop it!
Put on your fucking seatbelt!
Can you move your hands for me?
Now lift your arms.
Watch out for any neurological signs.
Motor function, coordination, diction.
As you know.
Could the plate move in her head?
No.
Not without violent impact.
It's very solid.
It's titanium.
Get off me, asshole!
Hands off, sir.
Touch with your eyes.
Can I get a selfie?
I'm Justine.
Ah!
Wait! Don't move.
Hang on, I got it.
So what's your name?
Do you beep at security?
No. Imagine having to
flash cops before every flight.
Does it hurt?
Not at all.
- We're waiting!
- Can't you see we're busy?
- You said it didn't hurt.
- Yanking always hurts!
Alexia, an autograph please.
Thanks.
I'm done.
Alexia!
Alexia, please.
Just an autograph.
Sorry, but I waited three hours...
We met at the boat show in Marseille.
Remember?
No, sorry. Good night.
Wait!
Can I get a kiss goodbye?
Sorry, I just wanted to say...
I think I'm in love with you.
You probably think I'm crazy.
I doubt you feel the same.
But maybe we could be friends,
and then see?
What do you think?
The Adrien Legrand case is
back in the news, 10 years to the day
since the boy went missing
in the Paris region.
The mystery remains.
Due to a lack of new evidence,
the attorney general
has closed the case.
The nightmare continues for the family...
the fire has been contained,
but the damage is considerable.
The campsite was destroyed
along with nearby houses.
A wave of panic grips the South,
after the discovery of another corpse
this Thursday.
A 47-year-old man
is the fourth victim this year.
Two other men and a woman were murdered
in similar circumstances.
The police
are asking the public to remain calm
and reinforcing their presence
on the ground.
The hypothesis of a serial killer
is not yet official,
but the call for witnesses
should shed some light.
The police are getting calls
from throughout France...
- You OK?
- My belly hurts.
- Your period?
- I'm not always on the rag.
Whatever.
Ask your dad to examine you.
- It's nothing.
- Wait, here.
First time with a girl?
You can move down, you know.
What the fuck?
Stop, it hurts!
Whatever.
Coming?
Are you kidding me?
Fuck!
What's wrong?
So what is it?
Crazy you didn't feel it sooner.
Ah!
What do you think you're doing?
Romain? What's going on?
Call the cops! Now!
Sorry, is the bathroom occupied?
How many of you are there?
What do you mean?
There's Cri-Cri, Romu,
Juju and me.
Are more coming?
Hope not.
I'm Alex.
Jérôme. Or Jupi, to my friends.
Who'd you come with?
Are you OK?
I'm so wiped.
I can lend you my bed.
Hey, last stop.
I'm not going any farther.
Maybe just a little farther?
ADRIEN LEGRAND
COMPUTER-AGED TO 17
MARIE-SOPHIE LUMIÈRES
COMPUTER-AGED TO 25
WANTED
SUSPECT UNDER INVESTIGATION
MISSING
Fuck...
Shit.
Fuck!
Ah!
We tried to reach the mother.
There's no mother.
I don't know where she is.
We're looking.
Are you OK?
You don't have to say anything.
Just nod or shake your head if you like.
- We'll do a DNA test.
- What for?
Think I can't recognize my own son?
Accident on Route 389.
Death on scene...
You haven't said a word.
Can't you say something?
Never mind.
You'll talk when you're ready.
Anyone hurts you, I kill 'em.
Got it?
Even if it's me.
I'd kill myself, I swear.
Captain!
I saved you some dinner.
After your long trip.
That's nice, thanks.
This is Adrien, my son.
He's my son.
Adrien, meet Rayane.
Conscience.
Everyone calls me that.
Go get some sleep, it's late.
- It's okay, I'm not on duty.
- Right.
But we're tired.
Of course. I know.
So, good night.
You too, Adrien.
Captain?
I'm happy for you.
Just came to say good night.
Sleeping in your clothes?
Here.
Whoa!
Give me your clothes.
Give them to me or I'll undress you.
Done yet?
Fucking hell!
C'mon!
God damn it!
Fuck this!
Stay put.
Turn around.
Show me.
There.
You're starting to look decent.
Hey.
Who's that?
You'll see.
Guys, the Captain's checking on us.
Is he some retard
who wants to live the dream?
For real? No, he's normal.
You know, like for some TV special?
- Know what I mean?
- Sure.
But what the fuck?
- Seriously.
- He's normal!
No, he's weird.
- Got a problem?
- No, Captain, just getting acquainted.
We'll take him to see the trucks.
A little advice, take it or leave it.
Fireman Legrand is my son.
And who am I to you?
I'm God.
So he's not only your brother,
he's Jesus.
Jesus will speak
when he has something to say.
And we'll listen. Got it?
Hey! Got it?
Yes, Captain.
That's better.
Turns out Jesus is white and gay!
Captain says believe, you believe.
C'mon, stop brown-nosing.
Rayane! Get down!
Four minutes on the stopwatch, Captain.
Take the kitchen.
I got the bedroom.
Copy.
Something wrong, Captain?
Control!
I don't get it.
All looks normal.
Okay, end simulation.
Will you ever speak?
Huh?
Just say "yes" like a normal person!
Even parrots can say yes!
No need to be human.
Even my phone says yes. Look.
- Say yes.
- Yes.
See? 20 euros for that shit.
What's that?
Show me.
Do I scare you?
I won't hurt you.
I just want to see.
Show me.
Hang on!
Stay, please. You'll see. Stay.
What's that?
What's that for?
You in a knitting club?
Wanna fight? Yeah?
Go on, fight like a man.
Fight like a man!
Go on.
Why do you always want to leave?
You're already home.
Here.
I brought back two or three hoes.
Biggest asses you ever saw!
Bitches be twerking, like...
Just give me a hole.
Black, Arab, whatever!
A hole is a hole!
I don't care, bring it on.
Hey, girl!
I'm talking to you! You hear me?
Girl!
Chill. Just wanna talk to you.
We won't hurt you.
Forget talking. Be direct, bruh.
I'd turn her around
and shove it in her ass.
Pussy, mouth, wherever she wants.
Even in her ear, bruh.
Hey, slut!
We say two words and
they think we wanna gang bang.
We're talking to you!
Turn around!
She thinks she's a star.
Go see her, grow some balls!
Go see her! Go on!
Dad?
Wake up, Dad.
Dad.
Adrien?
Adrien, are you up?
What... what are you doing?
Come. Come.
Sit down.
They can't tell me you're not my son.
He usually takes a sleeping pill, but...
he always wakes up in the morning, so...
I waited until 10, but...
at this point...
I don't know.
He must've taken one too many by accident.
Anyway...
I hope I didn't bother you for nothing.
I mean, I hope I did!
You know what I mean.
Did you go see?
No! I never go in his room.
He could be with a girlfriend.
I leave him alone.
How old is your son?
Forty-five.
Don't speak or touch anything.
Just watch.
Your usual.
Open up, honey. I'm with...
Allow me, ma'am.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Stay. You were upgraded.
So enjoy the show.
Rayane, we need to intubate, now.
What's wrong?
He's not breathing?
Adrien, help us!
Do you think he did it on purpose?
He didn't mean to...
Help me.
Fuck, now she's croaking!
Get backup.
Adrien, check her breathing.
That's my role.
Move it! Move!
Press her thorax 30 times.
Then plug her nose
and blow into her mouth.
Then start over.
Look at me. Know the Macarena?
We'll sing it together.
Follow me.
Press as hard as you can.
♪ Da, da-da-da, da-da-da
Macarena ♪
Cosa buena ♪
♪ Da, da-da-da, da-da-da
Macarena ♪
♪ Oh, Macarena ♪
Blow or she dies! Blow!
Go again.
♪ Da, da-da-da, da-da-da
Macarena ♪
Cosa buena ♪
♪ Da, da-da-da, da-da-da
Macarena ♪
♪ Oh, Macarena ♪
Blow.
Go again.
♪ Da, da-da-da, da-da-da
Macarena ♪
Cosa buena ♪
♪ Da, da-da-da, da-da-da
Macarena ♪
- He got her. Rayane, take over.
- Move.
Ma'am?
Wake up, ma'am!
Madam?
Go.
Where you from, for real?
I'm listening.
It's about your son.
We don't talk about my son.
- It's important.
- Don't talk about my son.
Ever.
Crawl back into the hole you came from!
You hear me?
Can't you feel the energy?
Between you and me?
Mom's here.
Not gonna kiss him?
How are you doing?
Are you adapting?
- Not too lost here?
- He doesn't talk.
I looked it up, it's normal.
Am I allowed to talk to him?
Sure, go ahead.
But he's fine here.
Go ahead.
We could go somewhere.
Just us two.
How do you do it?
Living here, next to his empty room.
His toys, his clothes...
Must be hell.
His smell still permeates the walls.
Why inflict that on yourself?
Give us a minute, please, honey.
I won't let you take him.
I don't want him, Vincent.
Ah.
Stop!
Please, please...
Stop, stop...
Please, stop.
If you were me?
If you couldn't mourn your kid,
what would you do?
Huh?
You poor thing.
You poor, poor thing.
What mess did you get yourself in?
Whatever your twisted reasons
for exploiting his fucking folly,
I don't care, just take care of him.
Look at me.
You take care of him.
He needs someone, you or another.
Say it.
Still no trace of the young woman
suspected in the series of murders
that has shaken the South this year.
The 32-year-old dancer...
Adrien, can you come?
Help me, please.
Wait!
Come help me, please.
Here.
I'm sick of twisting.
Shoot straight into the muscle.
Then press down.
Avoid bruises, if you pity your dad.
Are you sick?
No.
I'm old.
Stop!
Sorry.
I take care of you.
Not the other way round.
Sit down.
Do you trust me?
We'll make it grow.
Get down!
Ah!
- You okay?
- Yeah.
- Dizzy?
- No.
- Blurry vision?
- No!
- What's my name?
- Get me up!
No.
What's my name?
And her? Know her name?
They need you in back, Captain.
We secure and retreat?
Only one? Is it secured?
Captain!
Should we secure it first?
Hold this.
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
I don't care who you are.
You're my son.
You'll always be my son.
Whoever you are.
Is that clear?
Adrien! Adrien!
♪ I'm just a poor
Wayfaring stranger ♪
♪ Traveling through
This world of woe ♪
♪ Ain't no sickness
No toil, nor danger ♪
Go for it!
♪ In that bright land
To which I go ♪
♪ I'm going there
To see my Father ♪
♪ I'm only going over Jordan ♪
♪ I'm only going over home ♪
♪ I know dark clouds
Gonna gather 'round me ♪
♪ I know my way
Be rough and steep ♪
♪ Yet beautiful fields
Lie just before me ♪
♪ Where God's redeemed
Their vigils keep ♪
♪ I'm going there
To meet my mother ♪
No more to roam ♪
C'mon guys, shut it down!
Seen the time?
♪ I'm only going over home ♪
♪ I'll soon be free
From every trial ♪
♪ This form shall rest
Beneath the sun ♪
♪ I'll drop this cross of
Self-denial ♪
♪ And enter in
That home with God ♪
♪ I'm goin' home
To meet my Savior ♪
Ah!
What are you doing?
I love you.
I love you too.
Don't go, please!
I'm scared, don't leave me!
Push.
Push harder.
Look at me. Look at me!
You'll be okay. I'm here.
Push hard, Adrien.
My name's Alexia.
Push hard, Alexia.
Push!
How is it?
Alexia...
Alexia!
I'm here.
Stay with me.
Alexia?
I'm here.